Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Mapbox Legal Portal
===================

Terms of Service

Privacy Policy

Support Services

‍**Mapbox Privacy Policies**
============================

* ‍[Privacy Policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)
* ‍[Product Privacy Policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy)

[**‍**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy)**California Notices At Collection**

* ‍[Privacy Policy "California Notice At Collection"](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#[AIFCAIFC])

Privacy Policy
--------------

This privacy policy describes the personal data Mapbox and/or its affiliates (hereinafter collectively referred to as “Mapbox”) may receive and why such personal data may be received in its capacity as a data controller, how such personal data may be used (including whom it may be shared with and for what purposes), and choices about such personal data.    

This privacy policy applies to the extent Mapbox processes personal data in its capacity as a data controller under the GDPR (or “business” under the CCPA) when an individual: (a) visits and engages with any of Mapbox’s websites, (b) attends a virtual or in-person Mapbox event, (c) provides contact information for the purposes of Mapbox contacting about Mapbox products/services, (d) uses third-party websites or applications that cite this privacy policy, (e) provide billing information for Mapbox products/services account administration, or (f) apply to or are contacted about possible employment with Mapbox. Personal data is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household, as defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.100 et seq. and its implementing regulations (“CCPA”), or relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (hereinafter referred to as "personal data").

This Privacy Policy does not apply when Mapbox acts as a data processor.  Most Mapbox customer personal data is not governed by this policy. Mapbox operates in the capacity of a data processor for certain personal data when operating Mapbox’s  products/services that are purchased by developers and businesses to develop their own licensed applications. As such, customers/prospective customers should read Mapbox’s data processing addendum (“DPA”): [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa) which governs certain customer personal data that may be processed through use of Mapbox products/services including creation of a Mapbox products/services account. For other data not Processed by Mapbox as a Processor, e.g. billing and usage statistics data, see [**Mapbox's Product Privacy Policy**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy).

Corporate Accounts: If any account created with Mapbox lists a corporate email address for a company with which an individual is currently (or was formerly) employed (a “Corporate Email”), then the corporate entity to whom the Corporate Email pertains is responsible for privacy practices relating to use of Corporate Email. If Corporate Email is used within the scope of this privacy policy (as described at the top of this privacy policy), then this privacy policy applies.  For clarification, commonly known personal email account services (e.g., Gmail, Yahoo, Outlook) are not Corporate Email.  

### **Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**     

* **‍**Identifiers: Such as, name, address, email, phone number, Mapbox account username.
* Commercial information: Such as, transaction data including billing contact’s name, work phone number, work email, work address, professional title, and company name. 
* Financial data: Such as, credit card data is _not_ processed by Mapbox. Instead, credit card data is processed by Stripe, a third-party PCI-certified payment service provider, in accordance with its [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
* Internet or other network or device activity: When visiting any Mapbox websites, Mapbox automatically receives certain information such as: (a) browser and device type, (b) operating system, and (c) referring web pages including the pages visited on such sites. And information such as, IP address, data collected via strictly necessary and accepted website cookies / similar technologies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website, settings, and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* Employment data: Such as, education and employment history and other relevant personal data provided in an employment application submitted to Mapbox, information from a background check including information provided from reference checks.
* Location information: Such as, the location of an event where an individual signed up to receive communication or interact with Mapbox.
* User-generated content: Such as, a public comment provided by an individual in a Mapbox hosted webinar, Mapbox blog, or like Mapbox forum. For avoidance of doubt, an individual’s Mapbox product/service feedback does not constitute user-generated content. 
* Inference data about an individual: Such as, services Mapbox thinks an individual may be interested in based on prior purchases or website browsing, subject to the [Mapbox cookie policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 
* Other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with an individual: Such as, contents of correspondence with: 1) a Mapbox service provider in order to bill for items that may have been shipped upon an individual’s request as a result of the individual’s engagement with a Mapbox marketing campaign in person or virtually. 2) Mapbox, whether received through a form submitted on its website, conversation (in person, virtual, or phone call) with its staff, or via an email sent to an \[at\]mapbox email account. 3) And such as, personal data from entities who provide personal data about individuals, their job functions, and the companies they work for. Such entities attests to Mapbox that they have obtained all necessary consents and have lawful grounds to share such personal data with Mapbox.

### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data**      

##### **Mapbox uses personal data to:**       

* Provide, test, maintain/support, secure and improve Mapbox’s websites, to prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks, to calculate de-identified aggregate statistics, and for account administration/ billing purposes. 
* Send marketing information, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications (e.g., marketing newsletters, telemarketing calls, SMS or push notifications, information about Mapbox products, news or events) about Mapbox, its affiliates and partners.
* Plan or host virtual or in person events, contests, or other programs.
* Create and manage the recruitment system, job applications and a database of interested individuals and leads (including verifying the information provided to Mapbox) and assess and evaluate applicants skills and qualifications against the position(s) applied for.
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations.  
* Comply with applicable law.

### ‍**To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**    

##### **Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to provide any of the services, or related services to those, outlined in Section 2 of this privacy policy. However, prior to sharing personal data with such parties, Mapbox will have a written agreement consistent with the obligations outlined in applicable data protection laws and regulations.                                                                           
* Advertising and analytics partners. Any secondary use or sharing of personal data obtained through the use of third party cookies by these third parties is subject to their respective privacy policies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* In response to a request so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

### ‍**International Transfers**

Personal data may be processed by one or more Mapbox affiliates, processors, or service providers in order to operate Mapbox’s business – for example, in the United States for account administration and billing. Therefore, personal data may be processed outside of the location from which it was received. Mapbox ensures that the transfer of personal data offers an adequate level of protection and security, for instance by entering into the appropriate agreements that continuously ensure the same level of protective measures as set forth in applicable data protection laws and regulations and certification certification under the EU-US Data Privacy Framework, UK Extension to the EU-US Data Privacy Framework, and the Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework (collectively, the “Data Privacy Framework” or “DPF”), and, if required, standard contractual clauses or alternative mechanism for the transfer of data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR) or other applicable regulators or legislators. 

Mapbox’s Notice of Certification under the DPF, is available here: [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification)

##### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR INDIVIDUALS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

##### **4.1 Legal bases for processing personal data:** 

Some countries require that companies only process personal data if they have a “legal basis” (or justifiable need) to process personal data. To the extent those laws apply, Mapbox’s legal bases to process personal data are as follows:

* To comply with a legal obligation to which Mapbox, as a controller, is subject.
* To protect the vital interests of an individual or of another natural person.
* For the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Mapbox as the controller or by an independent third party controller, except where the individual’s interests or fundamental rights and freedoms override such interests.
* Performance of the contract.
* Consent.

In all cases of data processing on the basis of legitimate interests, Mapbox considers the impact on the rights and freedoms of the individuals whose data may be part of the processing, and ensures that its processing activities do not contradict or place at unreasonable risk any such rights or freedoms. Mapbox has assessed that these legitimate interests are not overridden by the data protection interests or fundamental rights of any individuals. In all cases, Mapbox ensures that such processing is legal, fair, and reasonable. 

### **Retention** 

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 of this privacy policy.

### **Security**

Mapbox takes steps designed to secure personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.  Unfortunately, no system is 100% secure, and Mapbox cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal data it receives.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Mapbox does not accept liability for unintentional or accidental destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access.**‍**

### **Children**

Mapbox products/services, websites, events, and other communications are not intended or directed to children under the age of 18 (or other age of majority as required by local law), and Mapbox does not knowingly collect personal data from children. If the parent or legal guardian learns that their child has provided Mapbox with personal data without their consent, then they should contact Mapbox as set forth below in the Contact Mapbox section of this privacy policy. If Mapbox learns that it has collected personal data in violation of applicable law, it will promptly take steps to delete such personal data.

### **Choices About Personal Data**

An individual may opt-out of processing of their personal data within the scope of this privacy policy at any time and prevent further Mapbox processing by contacting Mapbox as described below. 

* **Email and Telephone Communications:**

Click the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email received from Mapbox to opt out of receiving future commercial emails. Note that for current customers, Mapbox will continue to send non-promotional communications which may not be opted out of (e.g., communications regarding products/services or updates to Mapbox Terms or this privacy policy). Mapbox processes requests to be placed on do-not-mail, do-not-phone, and do-not-contact lists as required by applicable law.

* **Website logs and cookies:**

Devices have settings to delete stored cookies and most browsers have the option to decline cookies. However, certain parts of Mapbox’s website (including pages that require login) will not be accessible if Mapbox cookies (first party cookies) are not accepted. In contrast, third-party cookies set by third parties for marketing and analytics purposes on Mapbox’s website can be disabled, in principle, without affecting access. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit the Mapbox website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 

* **In accordance with applicable law, the individual to whom the personal data pertains may have the following rights regarding their personal data:**

* Access/view personal data  
* Portability of personal data in a commonly machine readable format 
* Correct personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete
* Deletion of personal data
* Restrict or object to processing of personal data
* Opt-out of the sale of personal data, if applicable, where such requests are permitted by law and as defined in the CCPA.

To exercise your right to deletion of personal data, please complete the form [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/ccpa-deletion-request#:~:text=To%20delete%20account%2Drelated%20information,you%20believe%20Mapbox%20obtained%20it.). For any other rights, please contact Mapbox at [privacy@mapbox.com](mailto:privacy@mapbox.com). In your email include  name, and request or question. To protect privacy, Mapbox will take steps to verify the identity of the requestor before fulfilling the request. Mapbox will process such requests in accordance with applicable laws. Although we encourage you to contact us if you have questions or complaints, you also have the right to lodge a complaint in the EU and UK with the appropriate supervisory authority in your jurisdiction. In some cases, these rights may be subject to exceptions, as permitted by applicable law. 

### **Additional Information For California Residents**

##### **9.1 California Notice At Collection:**

**Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**

* **‍**Identifiers: Such as, name, address, email, phone number, Mapbox account username.
* Commercial information: Such as, transaction data including billing contact’s name, work phone number, work email, work address, professional title, and company name. 
* Financial data: Such as, credit card data is _not_ processed by Mapbox. Instead, credit card data is processed by Stripe, a third-party PCI-certified payment service provider, in accordance with its [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
* Internet or other network or device activity: When visiting any Mapbox websites, Mapbox automatically receives certain information such as: (a) browser and device type, (b) operating system, and (c) referring web pages including the pages visited on such sites. And information such as, IP address, data collected via strictly necessary and accepted website cookies / similar technologies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website, settings, and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* Employment data: Such as, education and employment history and other relevant personal data provided in an employment application submitted to Mapbox, information from a background check including information provided from reference checks.
* Location information: Such as, the location of an event where an individual signed up to receive communication or interact with Mapbox.
* User-generated content: Such as, a public comment provided by an individual in a Mapbox hosted webinar, Mapbox blog, or like Mapbox forum. For avoidance of doubt, an individual’s Mapbox product/service feedback does not constitute user-generated content. 
* Inference data about an individual: Such as, services Mapbox thinks an individual may be interested in based on prior purchases or website browsing, subject to the [Mapbox cookie policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 
* Other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with an individual: Such as, contents of correspondence with: 1) a Mapbox service provider in order to bill for items that may have been shipped upon an individual’s request as a result of the individual’s engagement with a Mapbox marketing campaign in person or virtually. 2) Mapbox, whether received through a form submitted on its website, conversation (in person, virtual, or phone call) with its staff, or via an email sent to an \[at\]mapbox email account. 3) And such as, personal data from entities who provide personal data about individuals, their job functions, and the companies they work for. Such entities attests to Mapbox that they have obtained all necessary consents and have lawful grounds to share such personal data with Mapbox.

**How Mapbox Uses Personal Data** 

* Provide, test, maintain/support, secure and improve Mapbox’s websites, to prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks, to calculate de-identified aggregate statistics, and for account administration/ billing purposes. 
* Send marketing information, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications (e.g., marketing newsletters, telemarketing calls, SMS or push notifications, information about Mapbox products, news or events) about Mapbox, its affiliates and partners.
* Plan or host virtual or in person events, contests, or other programs.
* Create and manage the recruitment system, job applications and a database of interested individuals and leads (including verifying the information provided to Mapbox) and assess and evaluate applicants skills and qualifications against the position(s) applied for.
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations.  
* Comply with applicable law.

**To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**  

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to provide any of the services, or related services to those, outlined in Section 2 of this privacy policy. However, prior to sharing personal data with such parties, Mapbox will have a written agreement consistent with the obligations outlined in applicable data protection laws and regulations.                                                                           
* Advertising and analytics partners. Any secondary use or sharing of personal data obtained through the use of third party cookies by these third parties is subject to their respective privacy policies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* In response to a request so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

**Data Retention**

* Only for so long as Mapbox has a business purpose to retain and process such personal data.                                                      

### **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

Mapbox will update this privacy policy at its own discretion from time to time to reflect changes in Mapbox’s practices, technologies, legal requirements, and other factors. **‍**

### **Contact Mapbox** 

Mapbox would love to hear any questions, concerns, or feedback about this privacy policy or Mapbox’s data protection practices. Please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com.

* * *

**Mapbox Product Privacy Policy**
---------------------------------

**See Section 9 below for "California Notice At Collection"**

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers map and location services in a wide variety of web, mobile, game and embedded device applications. Mapbox customers are developers/companies who embed Mapbox software development kits (SDKs) or integrate with Mapbox application program interfaces (APIs) (collectively, “**Mapbox materials**”) in their licensed applications to enable maps and location features.  

**This product privacy policy** applies when Mapbox is processing personal data (sometimes referred to as personal information), from an end user of a licensed application (provided by Mapbox or one of its customers) that contains Mapbox materials, in its capacity (where legally applicable) as an independent data controller. For example, when Mapbox determines the purpose and means of processing such as making decisions about how to process personal data that benefits Mapbox customers generally, not just a single customer, Mapbox is processing as an independent data controller. In all cases, Mapbox’s processing of personal data continues to be controlled by its contracts with Mapbox customers, this product privacy policy and applicable data protection laws and regulations. 

Personal data is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, or relating to an identified or identifiable natural person, or data defined as personal information or personal data under applicable data protection laws and regulations (in this policy, referred to as "**personal data**”).

**Additional Privacy Policy:** Mapbox also processes as a data controller when individuals use any Mapbox website or engage with Mapbox marketing programs, including attending live or virtual events or applying for a job with Mapbox. Please see the applicable Mapbox privacy policy, available [here.](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)

### Personal Data Mapbox May Receive

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to its product development and operations in an effort to collect the least amount of personal data from the outset. The limited personal dataset that Mapbox may receive, outlined below, describes personal data categories and associated example data elements.  Please note, many data elements are only classified as personal data when combined with an associated IP address, other persistent identifier or data element capable of identifying or being reasonably linked to a natural person.

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

‍

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above categories of personal data, Mapbox may also collect the following categories of personal data (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

‍

### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data**

Mapbox does not process personal data for the purposes of identifying an individual or creating or maintaining records about an individual. Instead, Mapbox processes personal data to:       

* Provide, test, maintain, secure and improve Mapbox products and services, 
* Provide customer requested support, including applying knowledge gained from individual customer support requests to benefit all Mapbox customers, to the extent such knowledge is de-identified,
* Prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks,
* Administer/bill customers (not end users),
* Calculate de-identified aggregate statistics,
* Train artificial intelligence models (to the extent personal data is first de-identified), which is a set of technologies and processes that allow computers to learn, reason, and assist in decision making; such models are used to improve Mapbox products and services,
* Anonymize such data so it is no longer considered personal data,
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations, and 
* Comply with applicable law.

Mapbox processes de-identified data only in a de-identified form and does not permit attempts to re-identify such data or associate with a natural person.

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above uses of personal data, Mapbox may also use personal data in the following ways (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Mapbox uses personal data for purposes that are compatible with those stated above such as providing and supporting the service. For Dash branded products and services, machine learning to develop and improve and fine tune Mapbox’s models is one of those purposes.
* Third party independent controller vendors will process the data you provide to Dash branded products and services for their own purposes. For more information visit their respective privacy policies (linked in Section 3). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍

### **To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data** 

**Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to process in accordance  with Section 2 above. 
* In response to a request, so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its customers or their end users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or due diligence related thereto of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

Dash branded products and services: In addition to the above parties that Mapbox may disclose personal data to, Mapbox may also disclose personal data to the following third party independent controllers (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Certain functionality to instruct Dash branded products and services to process a question such as when the end user says “hey Dash” or touches the Dash branded products and services icon or starts typing a command. PicoVoice’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://picovoice.ai/docs/privacy-policy/  (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* On-device speech-to-text (“STT”) vendor (which Mapbox has no control over and is selected by the end user based on their device) will transpose audio speech spoken to Dash branded products and services to a string of text and send it to Mapbox servers to answer the end users question. The on-device STT processing is subject to its respective published privacy practices, which you should review. Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Large language model providers (“LLMs”), such as OpenAI review the end users voice input text and formulate a response to the end user. OpenAI’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://openai.com/policies/privacy-policy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Text-to-speech (“TTS”) vendors, such as Eleven labs transform the Mapbox appended LLM response to an audio MP3 file that is spoken (in audio form) to the requestor via Dash branded products and services. ElevenLabs processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://elevenlabs.io/privacy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍

### **International Transfers**

Personal data may be processed by one or more Mapbox affiliates, processors, or service providers in order to operate Mapbox’s business – for example, in the United States for account administration and billing. Therefore, personal data may be processed outside of the location from which it was received. Mapbox ensures that the transfer of personal data offers an adequate level of protection and security, for instance by entering into the appropriate agreements that continuously ensure the same level of protective measures as set forth in applicable data protection laws and regulations and certification certification under the EU-US, UK-US, Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework ("DPF"), and, if required, standard contractual clauses or alternative mechanism for the transfer of data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR) or other applicable regulators or legislators. 

Mapbox’s Notice of Certification under the DPF, is available here: [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification)

##### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR INDIVIDUALS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

##### **4.1 Legal bases for processing personal data:** 

Some countries require that companies only process personal data if they have a “legal basis” (or justifiable need) to process personal data. To the extent those laws apply, Mapbox’s legal bases to process personal data are as follows:

* To comply with a legal obligation to which Mapbox, as a controller, is subject.
* To protect the vital interests of an individual or of another natural person.
* For the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Mapbox as the controller or by an independent third party controller, except where the individual’s interests or fundamental rights and freedoms override such interests.
* Performance of the contract.
* Consent.

In all cases of data processing on the basis of legitimate interests, Mapbox considers the impact on the rights and freedoms of the individuals whose data may be part of the processing, and ensures that its processing activities do not contradict or place at unreasonable risk any such rights or freedoms. Mapbox has assessed that these legitimate interests are not overridden by the data protection interests or fundamental rights of any individuals. In all cases, Mapbox ensures that such processing is legal, fair, and reasonable. 

### **Retention** 

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as Mapbox determines it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 above. In determining how long to retain personal data, Mapbox considers the amount, nature and sensitivity of the data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data, the purposes for which personal data is processed, applicable legal requirements, and Mapbox’s legitimate interests. The purposes for which Mapbox processes data may dictate different retention periods for the same types of data. For example, Mapbox retains IP addresses for 30 days and after such time, in select instances, may need to extend such retention period for an investigation based on its legitimate interests to secure its products and services, prevent fraud and for legal compliance purposes.

### **Security**

Mapbox takes steps designed to secure personal data in accordance with this product privacy policy.  Unfortunately, no system is 100% secure, and Mapbox cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal data it receives.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Mapbox does not accept liability for unintentional or accidental destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access.

### **Children**

Mapbox products and services are not intended or directed to children under the age of 18 (or other age of majority as required by local law), and Mapbox does not knowingly collect personal data from children. If the parent or legal guardian learns that their child has provided Mapbox with personal data without their consent, then they should contact Mapbox as set forth below in the Contact Mapbox section of this product privacy policy. If Mapbox learns that it has collected personal data in violation of applicable data protection laws and regulations, it will promptly take steps to delete such personal data.

### **Choices About Personal Data** 

To the fullest extent possible, Mapbox will fulfill data subject rights requests provided it can match a data subject (natural person to whom the personal data in question pertains) to personal data that Mapbox processes. Mapbox does not, and is not required to, collect additional personal data in order to positively identify a data subject. 

As outlined in Section 1 above, Mapbox receives only minimal personal data and operates controls designed to promptly de-identify and anonymize such personal data. For example, Mapbox deletes IP addresses within 30 days of receipt (unless required for an investigation), so it is unlikely that Mapbox would have personal data capable of identifying a data subject after 30 days of receiving such data. However, if verifiable and detailed information is available, Mapbox will work with the data subject to determine if the request can reasonably be met. The data subject will need to provide a valid email address so that Mapbox can communicate and support the request, as well as any information that Mapbox determines may be needed to verify whether it holds any applicable personal data. 

**In accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations and depending upon the data subject’s residency, the data subject to whom the personal data pertains may have the right to request the following regarding certain of their personal data:**

* Access/view/know personal data  
* Portability of personal data in a commonly machine readable format 
* Correct personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete
* Deletion of certain personal data
* Restrict or object to processing of personal data
* Opt-out of the “sale” or “share” or processing for “targeted advertising” (each as defined by applicable data protection laws and regulations) of personal data , if applicable, where such requests are permitted by law

To request deletion of certain personal data, please complete the form [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/ccpa-deletion-request#:~:text=To%20delete%20account%2Drelated%20information,you%20believe%20Mapbox%20obtained%20it.). For any other request to exercise rights, please contact Mapbox at [privacy@mapbox.com](mailto:privacy@mapbox.com). The requesting email must come from the data subject to whom the personal data pertains and include the data subject’s name, email address and specific request or question. To protect privacy, Mapbox will take steps to verify the identity of the requestor before fulfilling the request. Mapbox will process such requests in accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations. 

To the extent required in the state where the data subject resides and where Mapbox has denied such data subject’s earlier request, the data subject may file an appeal with Mapbox for reconsideration. To file an appeal, please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com. The requesting email must come from the data subject to whom the personal data pertains and include the data subject’s name, email address and reference to the specific request and denial.

Mapbox encourages data subjects to contact it directly with any questions or complaints. However, Mapbox acknowledges and informs the data subject that they have the right to lodge a complaint in the EU and UK with the appropriate supervisory authority in the applicable jurisdiction; .; and in select United States states, to contact the respective state’s Attorney General’s Office, whose contact information may be identified here https://www.usa.gov/state-attorney-general (or successor link). In some cases, these rights may be subject to exceptions, as permitted by applicable law.

### **Additional Information For California Residents**

##### **9.1 California Notice At Collection:**

**Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to its product development and operations in an effort to collect the least amount of personal data from the outset. The limited personal dataset that Mapbox may receive, outlined below, describes personal data categories and associated example data elements.  Please note, many data elements are only classified as personal data when combined with an associated IP address, other persistent identifier or data element capable of identifying or being reasonably linked to a natural person.

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s company name (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name. |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(an IP address is not associated with such geolocation data and the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

‍

**Dash branded products and services:** In addition to the above categories of personal data, Mapbox may also collect the following categories of personal data (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

‍

##### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data** 

Mapbox does not process personal data for the purposes of identifying an individual or creating or maintaining records about an individual. Instead, Mapbox processes personal data to:       

* Provide, test, maintain, secure and improve Mapbox products and services, 
* Provide customer requested support, including applying knowledge gained from individual customer support requests to benefit all Mapbox customers, to the extent such knowledge is de-identified,
* Prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks,
* Administer/bill customers (not end users),
* Calculate de-identified aggregate statistics,
* Train artificial intelligence models (to the extent personal data is first de-identified), which is a set of technologies and processes that allow computers to learn, reason, and assist in decision making; such models are used to improve Mapbox products and services,
* Anonymize such data so it is no longer considered personal data,
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations, and 
* Comply with applicable law.

Mapbox processes de-identified data only in a de-identified form and does not permit attempts to re-identify such data or associate with a natural person.

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above uses of personal data, Mapbox may also use personal data in the following ways (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Mapbox uses personal data for purposes that are compatible with those stated above such as providing and supporting the service. For Dash branded products and services, machine learning to develop and improve and fine tune Mapbox’s models is one of those purposes.
* Third party independent controller vendors will process the data you provide to Dash branded products and services for their own purposes. For more information visit their respective privacy policies (linked in Section 3). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

##### **To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**  

**Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to process in accordance  with Section 2 above.
* In response to a request, so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its customers or their end users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or due diligence related thereto of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

**Dash branded products and services:** In addition to the above parties that Mapbox may disclose personal data to, Mapbox may also disclose personal data to the following third party independent controllers (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Certain functionality to instruct Dash branded products and services to process a question such as when the end user says “hey Dash” or touches the Dash branded products and services icon or starts typing a command. PicoVoice’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://picovoice.ai/docs/privacy-policy/  (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* On-device speech-to-text (“STT”) vendor (which Mapbox has no control over and is selected by the end user based on their device) will transpose audio speech spoken to Dash branded products and services to a string of text and send it to Mapbox servers to answer the end users question. The on-device STT processing is subject to its respective published privacy practices, which you should review. Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Large language model providers (“LLMs”), such as OpenAI review the end users voice input text and formulate a response to the end user. OpenAI’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://openai.com/policies/privacy-policy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Text-to-speech (“TTS”) vendors, such as Eleven labs transform the Mapbox appended LLM response to an audio MP3 file that is spoken (in audio form) to the requestor via Dash branded products and services. ElevenLabs processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://elevenlabs.io/privacy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍**Data Retention**

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as Mapbox determines it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 above. In determining how long to retain personal data, Mapbox considers the amount, nature and sensitivity of the data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data, the purposes for which personal data is processed, applicable legal requirements, and Mapbox’s legitimate interests. The purposes for which Mapbox processes data may dictate different retention periods for the same types of data. For example, Mapbox retains IP addresses for 30 days and after such time, in select instances, may need to extend such retention period for an investigation based on its legitimate interests to secure its products and services, prevent fraud and for legal compliance purposes.

### **Changes to this Product Privacy Policy**

Mapbox will update this product privacy policy at its own discretion from time to time to reflect changes in Mapbox’s practices, technologies, legal requirements, and other factors. 

### **Contact Mapbox** 

Mapbox would love to hear any questions, concerns, or feedback about this product privacy policy or Mapbox’s data protection practices. Please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com.

Heading 1
=========

Heading 2
---------

### Heading 3

#### Heading 4

##### Heading 5

###### Heading 6

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur.

> Block quote

Ordered list

1. Item 1
2. Item 2
3. Item 3

Unordered list

* Item A
* Item B
* Item C

**Bold text**

_Emphasis_

Superscript

Subscript

Privacy & Security FAQ
----------------------

Last Updated:  Aug 22, 2023

1\. What is Mapbox?

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

13\. More questions?

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

### Want to receive updates on our sub-processors?

Please subscribe below:

Stay tuned for updates!

Please enter an email address that includes @.

### PRODUCTS

### Maps

### Search

### Other

### \_

### Navigation

### Logistics

### Data

### solutions

### use cases

### Developers

### Resources

### Company

* [Careers
    
    HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)

All Rights Reserved © Mapbox

Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Products

Products

Products

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

Maps

Navigation

Search

Data

Self-Hosted

Maps

Maps

Maps

Navigation

Navigation

Navigation

Search

Search

Search

Data

Data

Data

Self-Hosted

Self-Hosted

Self-Hosted

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/global-cities-3d-landmarks)

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →

Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Maps Overview

NEW

Maps Overview

NEW

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Overview →

Overview →

Overview →

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

[Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)

Mapbox GL JS

NEW

Mapbox GL JS

NEW

NEW

Immersive maps for web

Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

Mobile Maps SDK

NEW

NEW

Powerful maps for iOS and Android

Studio

NEW

Studio

NEW

NEW

Beautiful, custom map designs

[Static Maps

NEW

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)[Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)

Static Maps

NEW

Static Maps

NEW

NEW

Embed map images

Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

Mapbox Tiling Service

NEW

NEW

Host and add custom map data

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →

Over 100 global cities with 3D landmarks in Mapbox Standard

Read more →

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/autopilot-map)

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →

Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services

Navigation Overview

NEW

Navigation Overview

NEW

NEW

Custom navigation services

Overview →

Overview →

Overview →

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)

Navigation for Automotive

NEW

Navigation for Automotive

NEW

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services

MapGPT

NEW

MapGPT

NEW

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant

Autopilot Map

NEW

Autopilot Map

NEW

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems

[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Navigation for Mobile

NEW

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android

Mapbox for EV

NEW

Mapbox for EV

NEW

NEW

EV navigation solutions

Matrix API

NEW

Matrix API

NEW

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →

Mapbox Autopilot Map allows vehicles to drive themselves on more roads

Read more →

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/search-anywhere-go-anywhere-empowering-users-with-the-mapbox-search-sdks)

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →

Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Search Overview

NEW

Search Overview

NEW

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Overview →

Overview →

Overview →

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)

Geocoding

NEW

Geocoding

NEW

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses

Search Box

NEW

Search Box

NEW

NEW

User-friendly search interface

[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Address Autofill

NEW

Address Autofill

NEW

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →

Search anywhere, go anywhere: Empowering users with the Mapbox Search SDKs

Read more →

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/blog/enhanced-data-coverage-with-mapbox-movement-v4)

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →

Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Data Overview

NEW

Data Overview

NEW

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Overview →

Overview →

Overview →

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)

Traffic Data

NEW

Traffic Data

NEW

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions

Movement Data

NEW

Movement Data

NEW

NEW

Population patterns through space and time

[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Boundaries

NEW

Boundaries

NEW

NEW

Official boundaries around the world

.webp)

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →

Enhanced data coverage with Mapbox Movement V4

Read more →

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →](#)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Atlas

NEW

Atlas

NEW

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →

New 3D urban environments improve location awareness

Read more →

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Solutions

Solutions

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)

Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business

Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business

Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information

Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information

Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data

Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data

[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps

Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps

Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations

Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations

Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place

Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place

[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)

On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance

On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance

Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures

Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures

[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)

Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence

Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence

Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions

Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

Developers

Developers

Developers

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

documentation

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

documentation

documentation

documentation

documentation

Maps

Maps

Navigation

Navigation

Search

Search

Data

Data

See All Docs →

See All Docs →

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

connect

connect

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

[Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs](https://discord.gg/uMpcC5RmJh)[Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/tagged/mapbox+mapbox-ios+mapbox-android)[Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases](https://github.com/mapbox)

Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs

Developer Discord

Online community to discuss projects and help fellow devs

Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions

Stack Overflow

Share and search technical questions and solutions

Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases

Github

Submit bugs, share requests, and track releases

[Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Developer Network

Contract independent developers](https://www.mapbox.com/developer-network)

Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance

Get Support

Self-serve resources, account help, and technical assistance

Developer Network

Contract independent developers

Developer Network

Contract independent developers

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

links

links

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

[Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources](https://www.mapbox.com/developers)[Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services](https://labs.mapbox.com/developer-cheatsheet/)[Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help](https://docs.mapbox.com/help/)

Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources

Developer Quickstart

Overview of developer resources

Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services

Developer Cheat Sheet

Snapshot overview of Mapbox services

Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help

Help & Troubleshooting

Find answers and get help

[API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/playground/)[Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox](https://docs.mapbox.com/resources/dev-tools/)[API Status

Real-time data on system performance](https://status.mapbox.com/)

API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox

API Playgrounds

Demo spaces to experiment with Mapbox

Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox

Developer Tools

Web-based tools to help build with Mapbox

API Status

Real-time data on system performance

API Status

Real-time data on system performance

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Company

Company

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

follow us

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Company

Company

[Who we are

About our company mission and history](https://www.mapbox.com/company)[What we value

About what drives us](https://www.mapbox.com/company/values)[What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data](https://www.mapbox.com/about/maps)

Who we are

About our company mission and history

Who we are

About our company mission and history

What we value

About what drives us

What we value

About what drives us

What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data

What we do

About Mapbox technologies and data

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

Careers

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox

How we support your career](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team

Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Work at Mapbox

HIRING

HIRING

Opportunities to join our team

Life at Mapbox

How we support your career

Life at Mapbox

How we support your career

Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone

Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Building a Mapbox for everyone

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

impact

impact

[Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility](https://www.mapbox.com/esg)[Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations](https://www.mapbox.com/community/impact)

Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility

Sustainability

Environmental and social responsibility

Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations

Social Impact

Support for non-profits and positive impact organizations

follow us

follow us

LinkedIn

LinkedIn

X

X

Youtube

Youtube

Instagram

Instagram

TikTok

TikTok

Discord

Discord

Github

Github

Blog

Blog

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Resources

Resources

Resources

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

News

News

[Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features

Blog

NEW

Blog

NEW

Stay updated on product launches and new features

Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources

Newsroom

The latest Mapbox news and press resources

Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events

Events

Connect with Mapbox at virtual and in-person events

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Learn

Learn

[Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase)[Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/webinars)[Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIHl9sd2brgvjBlSETKYDcg)

Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries

Customer Showcases

NEW

Customer Showcases

NEW

See customer use cases and impact across industries

Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox

Webinars

NEW

Webinars

NEW

Live and on-demand videos about building with Mapbox

Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more

Videos

NEW

Videos

NEW

How-to videos, developer spotlights, event recordings, and more

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

Get Help

Get Help

[Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help](https://www.mapbox.com/support)[Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors](https://www.mapbox.com/community/education)

Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help

Support

NEW

Support

NEW

Flexible options for fast and expert help

Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors

Education

NEW

Education

NEW

Resources for students and instructors

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

featured showcase

featured showcase

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →

Pricing

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

English

日本語

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

English

日本語

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Products

Products

Products

Maps

Navigation

Data

Self-Hosted

Search

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Back

Maps

[Maps Overview

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps](https://www.mapbox.com/maps)[Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-gljs)[Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android](https://www.mapbox.com/mobile-maps-sdk)[Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs](https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio)[Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data](https://www.mapbox.com/mts)[Static Maps

Embed map images](https://www.mapbox.com/static-maps)

Maps

Maps

Maps Overview

NEW

Maps Overview

NEW

NEW

Smooth, fast, cross-platform maps

Mapbox GL JS

Immersive maps for web

Mobile Maps SDK

Powerful maps for iOS and Android

Studio

Beautiful, custom map designs

Mapbox Tiling Service

Host and add custom map data

Static Maps

Embed map images

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Back

Navigation

[Navigation Overview

NEW

Custom navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation)[Navigation for Automotive

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-automotive)[Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android](https://www.mapbox.com/navigation-mobile)[MapGPT

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant](https://www.mapbox.com/mapgpt)[Autopilot Map

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems](https://www.mapbox.com/autopilot-map)[Mapbox for EV

NEW

EV navigation solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/ev)[Matrix API

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance](https://www.mapbox.com/matrix-api)

Navigation

Navigation

Navigation Overview

NEW

Navigation Overview

NEW

NEW

Custom navigation services

Navigation for Automotive

NEW

Navigation for Automotive

NEW

NEW

In-vehicle infotainment and navigation services

Navigation for Mobile

NEW

Navigation for Mobile

NEW

NEW

Routing and directions for iOS & Android

MapGPT

NEW

MapGPT

NEW

NEW

A location-intelligent AI assistant

Autopilot Map

NEW

Autopilot Map

NEW

NEW

Precision data for autopilot systems

Mapbox for EV

NEW

Mapbox for EV

NEW

NEW

EV navigation solutions

Matrix API

NEW

Matrix API

NEW

NEW

Calculate travel time and distance

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Back

Search

[Search Overview

NEW

Smart location data and search features](https://www.mapbox.com/search-service)[Geocoding

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses](https://www.mapbox.com/geocoding)[Search Box

NEW

User-friendly search interface](https://www.mapbox.com/search-box)[Address Autofill

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms](https://www.mapbox.com/address-autofill)

Search

Search

Search Overview

NEW

Search Overview

NEW

NEW

Smart location data and search features

Geocoding

NEW

Geocoding

NEW

NEW

Geolocate and validate addresses

Search Box

NEW

Search Box

NEW

NEW

User-friendly search interface

Address Autofill

NEW

Address Autofill

NEW

NEW

Autocomplete for address forms

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Back

Data

[Data Overview

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets](https://www.mapbox.com/data-products)[Traffic Data

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions](https://www.mapbox.com/traffic-data)[Movement Data

NEW

Population patterns through space and time](https://www.mapbox.com/movement-data)[Boundaries

NEW

Official boundaries around the world](https://www.mapbox.com/boundaries)

Data

Data

Data Overview

NEW

Data Overview

NEW

NEW

Unique, high-value geospatial datasets

Traffic Data

NEW

Traffic Data

NEW

NEW

Live and typical traffic conditions

Movement Data

NEW

Movement Data

NEW

NEW

Population patterns through space and time

Boundaries

NEW

Boundaries

NEW

NEW

Official boundaries around the world

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Back

Self-Hosted

[Atlas

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/atlas)

Self-Hosted

Self-Hosted

Atlas

NEW

Atlas

NEW

NEW

On-premise or private cloud solutions

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Solutions

Solutions

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

[Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business](https://www.mapbox.com/logistics)[Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps](https://www.mapbox.com/automotive)[On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance](https://www.mapbox.com/on-demand-delivery)[Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence](https://www.mapbox.com/business-intelligence)[Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information](https://www.mapbox.com/weather)[Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations](https://www.mapbox.com/telco)[Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/outdoors)[Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions](https://www.mapbox.com/retail)[Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data](https://www.mapbox.com/real-estate)[Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place](https://www.mapbox.com/industries/travel)

Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business

Logistics

Simplify every phase of running a delivery business

Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps

Automotive

Integrated navigation experiences for in-vehicle and companion apps

On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance

On-Demand Logistics

Boost customer satisfaction and delivery performance

Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence

Business Intelligence

Enhance data analysis with location intelligence

Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information

Weather

Deliver accurate, real-time weather information

Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations

Telecommunications

Map real-time coverage and optimize network operations

Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures

Outdoors

Detailed maps for athletes and adventures

Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions

Retail

On-brand store locators and e-commerce solutions

Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data

Real Estate

Visualize property listings, rentals, and market data

Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place

Travel

Plan, book, and explore the world all in one place

Developers

documentation

connect

links

Developers

Developers

documentation

connect

links

documentation

connect

links

documentation

documentation

documentation

Maps

Maps

Navigation

Navigation

Search

Search

Data

Data

See All Docs →

See All Docs →

connect

connect

connect

Developer Discord

Developer Discord

Stack Overflow

Stack Overflow

Github

Github

Get Support

Get Support

Developer Network

Developer Network

links

links

links

Developer Quickstart

Developer Quickstart

Developer Cheat Sheet

Developer Cheat Sheet

Help & Troubleshooting

Help & Troubleshooting

API Playgrounds

API Playgrounds

Developer Tools

Developer Tools

API Status

API Status

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

Company

Company

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

company

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

impact

follow us

company

company

company

Who we are

Who we are

What we value

What we value

What we do

What we do

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

Careers

Careers

[Work at Mapbox

HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)[Life at Mapbox](https://www.mapbox.com/company/culture)[Diversity, Equity & Inclusion](https://www.mapbox.com/dei)

Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Work at Mapbox

HIRING

Life at Mapbox

Life at Mapbox

Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

Diversity, Equity & Inclusion

impact

impact

impact

Sustainability

Sustainability

Social Impact

Social Impact

follow us

follow us

follow us

LinkedIn

LinkedIn

X

X

Youtube

Youtube

Discord

Discord

Instagram

Instagram

TikTok

TikTok

Github

Github

Blog

Blog

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

Resources

Resources

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

learn

get help

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

News

News

[Blog](https://www.mapbox.com/blog)[Newsroom

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/newsroom)[Events

NEW](https://www.mapbox.com/events)

Blog

Blog

Newsroom

NEW

Newsroom

NEW

Events

NEW

Events

NEW

learn

learn

learn

Customer Showcases

Customer Showcases

Webinars

Webinars

Videos

Videos

get help

get help

get help

Support

Support

Education

Education

featured showcase

[

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →](https://www.mapbox.com/showcase/mapspeople)

featured showcase

featured showcase

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →

Indoor map innovation powered by Mapbox 3D visualizations...

Read more →

Pricing

Contact Us

Mapbox Legal Portal
===================

Mapbox Legal Portal
===================

Mapbox Legal Portal
===================

Terms of Service

Privacy Policy

Support Services

Terms of Service

Terms of Service

Terms of Service

Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Support Services

Support Services

Support Services

‍**Mapbox Privacy Policies**
============================

* ‍[Privacy Policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)
* ‍[Product Privacy Policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy)

[**‍**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy)**California Notices At Collection**

* ‍[Privacy Policy "California Notice At Collection"](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#[AIFCAIFC])

Privacy Policy
--------------

This privacy policy describes the personal data Mapbox and/or its affiliates (hereinafter collectively referred to as “Mapbox”) may receive and why such personal data may be received in its capacity as a data controller, how such personal data may be used (including whom it may be shared with and for what purposes), and choices about such personal data.    

This privacy policy applies to the extent Mapbox processes personal data in its capacity as a data controller under the GDPR (or “business” under the CCPA) when an individual: (a) visits and engages with any of Mapbox’s websites, (b) attends a virtual or in-person Mapbox event, (c) provides contact information for the purposes of Mapbox contacting about Mapbox products/services, (d) uses third-party websites or applications that cite this privacy policy, (e) provide billing information for Mapbox products/services account administration, or (f) apply to or are contacted about possible employment with Mapbox. Personal data is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household, as defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.100 et seq. and its implementing regulations (“CCPA”), or relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (hereinafter referred to as "personal data").

This Privacy Policy does not apply when Mapbox acts as a data processor.  Most Mapbox customer personal data is not governed by this policy. Mapbox operates in the capacity of a data processor for certain personal data when operating Mapbox’s  products/services that are purchased by developers and businesses to develop their own licensed applications. As such, customers/prospective customers should read Mapbox’s data processing addendum (“DPA”): [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa) which governs certain customer personal data that may be processed through use of Mapbox products/services including creation of a Mapbox products/services account. For other data not Processed by Mapbox as a Processor, e.g. billing and usage statistics data, see [**Mapbox's Product Privacy Policy**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy).

Corporate Accounts: If any account created with Mapbox lists a corporate email address for a company with which an individual is currently (or was formerly) employed (a “Corporate Email”), then the corporate entity to whom the Corporate Email pertains is responsible for privacy practices relating to use of Corporate Email. If Corporate Email is used within the scope of this privacy policy (as described at the top of this privacy policy), then this privacy policy applies.  For clarification, commonly known personal email account services (e.g., Gmail, Yahoo, Outlook) are not Corporate Email.  

### **Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**     

* **‍**Identifiers: Such as, name, address, email, phone number, Mapbox account username.
* Commercial information: Such as, transaction data including billing contact’s name, work phone number, work email, work address, professional title, and company name. 
* Financial data: Such as, credit card data is _not_ processed by Mapbox. Instead, credit card data is processed by Stripe, a third-party PCI-certified payment service provider, in accordance with its [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
* Internet or other network or device activity: When visiting any Mapbox websites, Mapbox automatically receives certain information such as: (a) browser and device type, (b) operating system, and (c) referring web pages including the pages visited on such sites. And information such as, IP address, data collected via strictly necessary and accepted website cookies / similar technologies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website, settings, and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* Employment data: Such as, education and employment history and other relevant personal data provided in an employment application submitted to Mapbox, information from a background check including information provided from reference checks.
* Location information: Such as, the location of an event where an individual signed up to receive communication or interact with Mapbox.
* User-generated content: Such as, a public comment provided by an individual in a Mapbox hosted webinar, Mapbox blog, or like Mapbox forum. For avoidance of doubt, an individual’s Mapbox product/service feedback does not constitute user-generated content. 
* Inference data about an individual: Such as, services Mapbox thinks an individual may be interested in based on prior purchases or website browsing, subject to the [Mapbox cookie policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 
* Other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with an individual: Such as, contents of correspondence with: 1) a Mapbox service provider in order to bill for items that may have been shipped upon an individual’s request as a result of the individual’s engagement with a Mapbox marketing campaign in person or virtually. 2) Mapbox, whether received through a form submitted on its website, conversation (in person, virtual, or phone call) with its staff, or via an email sent to an \[at\]mapbox email account. 3) And such as, personal data from entities who provide personal data about individuals, their job functions, and the companies they work for. Such entities attests to Mapbox that they have obtained all necessary consents and have lawful grounds to share such personal data with Mapbox.

### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data**      

##### **Mapbox uses personal data to:**       

* Provide, test, maintain/support, secure and improve Mapbox’s websites, to prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks, to calculate de-identified aggregate statistics, and for account administration/ billing purposes. 
* Send marketing information, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications (e.g., marketing newsletters, telemarketing calls, SMS or push notifications, information about Mapbox products, news or events) about Mapbox, its affiliates and partners.
* Plan or host virtual or in person events, contests, or other programs.
* Create and manage the recruitment system, job applications and a database of interested individuals and leads (including verifying the information provided to Mapbox) and assess and evaluate applicants skills and qualifications against the position(s) applied for.
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations.  
* Comply with applicable law.

### ‍**To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**    

##### **Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to provide any of the services, or related services to those, outlined in Section 2 of this privacy policy. However, prior to sharing personal data with such parties, Mapbox will have a written agreement consistent with the obligations outlined in applicable data protection laws and regulations.                                                                           
* Advertising and analytics partners. Any secondary use or sharing of personal data obtained through the use of third party cookies by these third parties is subject to their respective privacy policies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* In response to a request so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

### ‍**International Transfers**

Personal data may be processed by one or more Mapbox affiliates, processors, or service providers in order to operate Mapbox’s business – for example, in the United States for account administration and billing. Therefore, personal data may be processed outside of the location from which it was received. Mapbox ensures that the transfer of personal data offers an adequate level of protection and security, for instance by entering into the appropriate agreements that continuously ensure the same level of protective measures as set forth in applicable data protection laws and regulations and certification certification under the EU-US Data Privacy Framework, UK Extension to the EU-US Data Privacy Framework, and the Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework (collectively, the “Data Privacy Framework” or “DPF”), and, if required, standard contractual clauses or alternative mechanism for the transfer of data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR) or other applicable regulators or legislators. 

Mapbox’s Notice of Certification under the DPF, is available here: [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification)

##### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR INDIVIDUALS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

##### **4.1 Legal bases for processing personal data:** 

Some countries require that companies only process personal data if they have a “legal basis” (or justifiable need) to process personal data. To the extent those laws apply, Mapbox’s legal bases to process personal data are as follows:

* To comply with a legal obligation to which Mapbox, as a controller, is subject.
* To protect the vital interests of an individual or of another natural person.
* For the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Mapbox as the controller or by an independent third party controller, except where the individual’s interests or fundamental rights and freedoms override such interests.
* Performance of the contract.
* Consent.

In all cases of data processing on the basis of legitimate interests, Mapbox considers the impact on the rights and freedoms of the individuals whose data may be part of the processing, and ensures that its processing activities do not contradict or place at unreasonable risk any such rights or freedoms. Mapbox has assessed that these legitimate interests are not overridden by the data protection interests or fundamental rights of any individuals. In all cases, Mapbox ensures that such processing is legal, fair, and reasonable. 

### **Retention** 

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 of this privacy policy.

### **Security**

Mapbox takes steps designed to secure personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.  Unfortunately, no system is 100% secure, and Mapbox cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal data it receives.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Mapbox does not accept liability for unintentional or accidental destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access.**‍**

### **Children**

Mapbox products/services, websites, events, and other communications are not intended or directed to children under the age of 18 (or other age of majority as required by local law), and Mapbox does not knowingly collect personal data from children. If the parent or legal guardian learns that their child has provided Mapbox with personal data without their consent, then they should contact Mapbox as set forth below in the Contact Mapbox section of this privacy policy. If Mapbox learns that it has collected personal data in violation of applicable law, it will promptly take steps to delete such personal data.

### **Choices About Personal Data**

An individual may opt-out of processing of their personal data within the scope of this privacy policy at any time and prevent further Mapbox processing by contacting Mapbox as described below. 

* **Email and Telephone Communications:**

Click the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email received from Mapbox to opt out of receiving future commercial emails. Note that for current customers, Mapbox will continue to send non-promotional communications which may not be opted out of (e.g., communications regarding products/services or updates to Mapbox Terms or this privacy policy). Mapbox processes requests to be placed on do-not-mail, do-not-phone, and do-not-contact lists as required by applicable law.

* **Website logs and cookies:**

Devices have settings to delete stored cookies and most browsers have the option to decline cookies. However, certain parts of Mapbox’s website (including pages that require login) will not be accessible if Mapbox cookies (first party cookies) are not accepted. In contrast, third-party cookies set by third parties for marketing and analytics purposes on Mapbox’s website can be disabled, in principle, without affecting access. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit the Mapbox website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 

* **In accordance with applicable law, the individual to whom the personal data pertains may have the following rights regarding their personal data:**

* Access/view personal data  
* Portability of personal data in a commonly machine readable format 
* Correct personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete
* Deletion of personal data
* Restrict or object to processing of personal data
* Opt-out of the sale of personal data, if applicable, where such requests are permitted by law and as defined in the CCPA.

To exercise your right to deletion of personal data, please complete the form [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/ccpa-deletion-request#:~:text=To%20delete%20account%2Drelated%20information,you%20believe%20Mapbox%20obtained%20it.). For any other rights, please contact Mapbox at [privacy@mapbox.com](mailto:privacy@mapbox.com). In your email include  name, and request or question. To protect privacy, Mapbox will take steps to verify the identity of the requestor before fulfilling the request. Mapbox will process such requests in accordance with applicable laws. Although we encourage you to contact us if you have questions or complaints, you also have the right to lodge a complaint in the EU and UK with the appropriate supervisory authority in your jurisdiction. In some cases, these rights may be subject to exceptions, as permitted by applicable law. 

### **Additional Information For California Residents**

##### **9.1 California Notice At Collection:**

**Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**

* **‍**Identifiers: Such as, name, address, email, phone number, Mapbox account username.
* Commercial information: Such as, transaction data including billing contact’s name, work phone number, work email, work address, professional title, and company name. 
* Financial data: Such as, credit card data is _not_ processed by Mapbox. Instead, credit card data is processed by Stripe, a third-party PCI-certified payment service provider, in accordance with its [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
* Internet or other network or device activity: When visiting any Mapbox websites, Mapbox automatically receives certain information such as: (a) browser and device type, (b) operating system, and (c) referring web pages including the pages visited on such sites. And information such as, IP address, data collected via strictly necessary and accepted website cookies / similar technologies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website, settings, and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* Employment data: Such as, education and employment history and other relevant personal data provided in an employment application submitted to Mapbox, information from a background check including information provided from reference checks.
* Location information: Such as, the location of an event where an individual signed up to receive communication or interact with Mapbox.
* User-generated content: Such as, a public comment provided by an individual in a Mapbox hosted webinar, Mapbox blog, or like Mapbox forum. For avoidance of doubt, an individual’s Mapbox product/service feedback does not constitute user-generated content. 
* Inference data about an individual: Such as, services Mapbox thinks an individual may be interested in based on prior purchases or website browsing, subject to the [Mapbox cookie policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 
* Other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with an individual: Such as, contents of correspondence with: 1) a Mapbox service provider in order to bill for items that may have been shipped upon an individual’s request as a result of the individual’s engagement with a Mapbox marketing campaign in person or virtually. 2) Mapbox, whether received through a form submitted on its website, conversation (in person, virtual, or phone call) with its staff, or via an email sent to an \[at\]mapbox email account. 3) And such as, personal data from entities who provide personal data about individuals, their job functions, and the companies they work for. Such entities attests to Mapbox that they have obtained all necessary consents and have lawful grounds to share such personal data with Mapbox.

**How Mapbox Uses Personal Data** 

* Provide, test, maintain/support, secure and improve Mapbox’s websites, to prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks, to calculate de-identified aggregate statistics, and for account administration/ billing purposes. 
* Send marketing information, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications (e.g., marketing newsletters, telemarketing calls, SMS or push notifications, information about Mapbox products, news or events) about Mapbox, its affiliates and partners.
* Plan or host virtual or in person events, contests, or other programs.
* Create and manage the recruitment system, job applications and a database of interested individuals and leads (including verifying the information provided to Mapbox) and assess and evaluate applicants skills and qualifications against the position(s) applied for.
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations.  
* Comply with applicable law.

**To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**  

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to provide any of the services, or related services to those, outlined in Section 2 of this privacy policy. However, prior to sharing personal data with such parties, Mapbox will have a written agreement consistent with the obligations outlined in applicable data protection laws and regulations.                                                                           
* Advertising and analytics partners. Any secondary use or sharing of personal data obtained through the use of third party cookies by these third parties is subject to their respective privacy policies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* In response to a request so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

**Data Retention**

* Only for so long as Mapbox has a business purpose to retain and process such personal data.                                                      

### **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

Mapbox will update this privacy policy at its own discretion from time to time to reflect changes in Mapbox’s practices, technologies, legal requirements, and other factors. **‍**

### **Contact Mapbox** 

Mapbox would love to hear any questions, concerns, or feedback about this privacy policy or Mapbox’s data protection practices. Please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com.

* * *

**Mapbox Product Privacy Policy**
---------------------------------

**See Section 9 below for "California Notice At Collection"**

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers map and location services in a wide variety of web, mobile, game and embedded device applications. Mapbox customers are developers/companies who embed Mapbox software development kits (SDKs) or integrate with Mapbox application program interfaces (APIs) (collectively, “**Mapbox materials**”) in their licensed applications to enable maps and location features.  

**This product privacy policy** applies when Mapbox is processing personal data (sometimes referred to as personal information), from an end user of a licensed application (provided by Mapbox or one of its customers) that contains Mapbox materials, in its capacity (where legally applicable) as an independent data controller. For example, when Mapbox determines the purpose and means of processing such as making decisions about how to process personal data that benefits Mapbox customers generally, not just a single customer, Mapbox is processing as an independent data controller. In all cases, Mapbox’s processing of personal data continues to be controlled by its contracts with Mapbox customers, this product privacy policy and applicable data protection laws and regulations. 

Personal data is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, or relating to an identified or identifiable natural person, or data defined as personal information or personal data under applicable data protection laws and regulations (in this policy, referred to as "**personal data**”).

**Additional Privacy Policy:** Mapbox also processes as a data controller when individuals use any Mapbox website or engage with Mapbox marketing programs, including attending live or virtual events or applying for a job with Mapbox. Please see the applicable Mapbox privacy policy, available [here.](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)

### Personal Data Mapbox May Receive

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to its product development and operations in an effort to collect the least amount of personal data from the outset. The limited personal dataset that Mapbox may receive, outlined below, describes personal data categories and associated example data elements.  Please note, many data elements are only classified as personal data when combined with an associated IP address, other persistent identifier or data element capable of identifying or being reasonably linked to a natural person.

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

‍

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above categories of personal data, Mapbox may also collect the following categories of personal data (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

‍

### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data**

Mapbox does not process personal data for the purposes of identifying an individual or creating or maintaining records about an individual. Instead, Mapbox processes personal data to:       

* Provide, test, maintain, secure and improve Mapbox products and services, 
* Provide customer requested support, including applying knowledge gained from individual customer support requests to benefit all Mapbox customers, to the extent such knowledge is de-identified,
* Prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks,
* Administer/bill customers (not end users),
* Calculate de-identified aggregate statistics,
* Train artificial intelligence models (to the extent personal data is first de-identified), which is a set of technologies and processes that allow computers to learn, reason, and assist in decision making; such models are used to improve Mapbox products and services,
* Anonymize such data so it is no longer considered personal data,
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations, and 
* Comply with applicable law.

Mapbox processes de-identified data only in a de-identified form and does not permit attempts to re-identify such data or associate with a natural person.

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above uses of personal data, Mapbox may also use personal data in the following ways (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Mapbox uses personal data for purposes that are compatible with those stated above such as providing and supporting the service. For Dash branded products and services, machine learning to develop and improve and fine tune Mapbox’s models is one of those purposes.
* Third party independent controller vendors will process the data you provide to Dash branded products and services for their own purposes. For more information visit their respective privacy policies (linked in Section 3). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍

### **To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data** 

**Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to process in accordance  with Section 2 above. 
* In response to a request, so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its customers or their end users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or due diligence related thereto of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

Dash branded products and services: In addition to the above parties that Mapbox may disclose personal data to, Mapbox may also disclose personal data to the following third party independent controllers (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Certain functionality to instruct Dash branded products and services to process a question such as when the end user says “hey Dash” or touches the Dash branded products and services icon or starts typing a command. PicoVoice’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://picovoice.ai/docs/privacy-policy/  (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* On-device speech-to-text (“STT”) vendor (which Mapbox has no control over and is selected by the end user based on their device) will transpose audio speech spoken to Dash branded products and services to a string of text and send it to Mapbox servers to answer the end users question. The on-device STT processing is subject to its respective published privacy practices, which you should review. Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Large language model providers (“LLMs”), such as OpenAI review the end users voice input text and formulate a response to the end user. OpenAI’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://openai.com/policies/privacy-policy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Text-to-speech (“TTS”) vendors, such as Eleven labs transform the Mapbox appended LLM response to an audio MP3 file that is spoken (in audio form) to the requestor via Dash branded products and services. ElevenLabs processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://elevenlabs.io/privacy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍

### **International Transfers**

Personal data may be processed by one or more Mapbox affiliates, processors, or service providers in order to operate Mapbox’s business – for example, in the United States for account administration and billing. Therefore, personal data may be processed outside of the location from which it was received. Mapbox ensures that the transfer of personal data offers an adequate level of protection and security, for instance by entering into the appropriate agreements that continuously ensure the same level of protective measures as set forth in applicable data protection laws and regulations and certification certification under the EU-US, UK-US, Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework ("DPF"), and, if required, standard contractual clauses or alternative mechanism for the transfer of data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR) or other applicable regulators or legislators. 

Mapbox’s Notice of Certification under the DPF, is available here: [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification)

##### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR INDIVIDUALS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

##### **4.1 Legal bases for processing personal data:** 

Some countries require that companies only process personal data if they have a “legal basis” (or justifiable need) to process personal data. To the extent those laws apply, Mapbox’s legal bases to process personal data are as follows:

* To comply with a legal obligation to which Mapbox, as a controller, is subject.
* To protect the vital interests of an individual or of another natural person.
* For the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Mapbox as the controller or by an independent third party controller, except where the individual’s interests or fundamental rights and freedoms override such interests.
* Performance of the contract.
* Consent.

In all cases of data processing on the basis of legitimate interests, Mapbox considers the impact on the rights and freedoms of the individuals whose data may be part of the processing, and ensures that its processing activities do not contradict or place at unreasonable risk any such rights or freedoms. Mapbox has assessed that these legitimate interests are not overridden by the data protection interests or fundamental rights of any individuals. In all cases, Mapbox ensures that such processing is legal, fair, and reasonable. 

### **Retention** 

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as Mapbox determines it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 above. In determining how long to retain personal data, Mapbox considers the amount, nature and sensitivity of the data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data, the purposes for which personal data is processed, applicable legal requirements, and Mapbox’s legitimate interests. The purposes for which Mapbox processes data may dictate different retention periods for the same types of data. For example, Mapbox retains IP addresses for 30 days and after such time, in select instances, may need to extend such retention period for an investigation based on its legitimate interests to secure its products and services, prevent fraud and for legal compliance purposes.

### **Security**

Mapbox takes steps designed to secure personal data in accordance with this product privacy policy.  Unfortunately, no system is 100% secure, and Mapbox cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal data it receives.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Mapbox does not accept liability for unintentional or accidental destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access.

### **Children**

Mapbox products and services are not intended or directed to children under the age of 18 (or other age of majority as required by local law), and Mapbox does not knowingly collect personal data from children. If the parent or legal guardian learns that their child has provided Mapbox with personal data without their consent, then they should contact Mapbox as set forth below in the Contact Mapbox section of this product privacy policy. If Mapbox learns that it has collected personal data in violation of applicable data protection laws and regulations, it will promptly take steps to delete such personal data.

### **Choices About Personal Data** 

To the fullest extent possible, Mapbox will fulfill data subject rights requests provided it can match a data subject (natural person to whom the personal data in question pertains) to personal data that Mapbox processes. Mapbox does not, and is not required to, collect additional personal data in order to positively identify a data subject. 

As outlined in Section 1 above, Mapbox receives only minimal personal data and operates controls designed to promptly de-identify and anonymize such personal data. For example, Mapbox deletes IP addresses within 30 days of receipt (unless required for an investigation), so it is unlikely that Mapbox would have personal data capable of identifying a data subject after 30 days of receiving such data. However, if verifiable and detailed information is available, Mapbox will work with the data subject to determine if the request can reasonably be met. The data subject will need to provide a valid email address so that Mapbox can communicate and support the request, as well as any information that Mapbox determines may be needed to verify whether it holds any applicable personal data. 

**In accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations and depending upon the data subject’s residency, the data subject to whom the personal data pertains may have the right to request the following regarding certain of their personal data:**

* Access/view/know personal data  
* Portability of personal data in a commonly machine readable format 
* Correct personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete
* Deletion of certain personal data
* Restrict or object to processing of personal data
* Opt-out of the “sale” or “share” or processing for “targeted advertising” (each as defined by applicable data protection laws and regulations) of personal data , if applicable, where such requests are permitted by law

To request deletion of certain personal data, please complete the form [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/ccpa-deletion-request#:~:text=To%20delete%20account%2Drelated%20information,you%20believe%20Mapbox%20obtained%20it.). For any other request to exercise rights, please contact Mapbox at [privacy@mapbox.com](mailto:privacy@mapbox.com). The requesting email must come from the data subject to whom the personal data pertains and include the data subject’s name, email address and specific request or question. To protect privacy, Mapbox will take steps to verify the identity of the requestor before fulfilling the request. Mapbox will process such requests in accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations. 

To the extent required in the state where the data subject resides and where Mapbox has denied such data subject’s earlier request, the data subject may file an appeal with Mapbox for reconsideration. To file an appeal, please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com. The requesting email must come from the data subject to whom the personal data pertains and include the data subject’s name, email address and reference to the specific request and denial.

Mapbox encourages data subjects to contact it directly with any questions or complaints. However, Mapbox acknowledges and informs the data subject that they have the right to lodge a complaint in the EU and UK with the appropriate supervisory authority in the applicable jurisdiction; .; and in select United States states, to contact the respective state’s Attorney General’s Office, whose contact information may be identified here https://www.usa.gov/state-attorney-general (or successor link). In some cases, these rights may be subject to exceptions, as permitted by applicable law.

### **Additional Information For California Residents**

##### **9.1 California Notice At Collection:**

**Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to its product development and operations in an effort to collect the least amount of personal data from the outset. The limited personal dataset that Mapbox may receive, outlined below, describes personal data categories and associated example data elements.  Please note, many data elements are only classified as personal data when combined with an associated IP address, other persistent identifier or data element capable of identifying or being reasonably linked to a natural person.

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s company name (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name. |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(an IP address is not associated with such geolocation data and the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

‍

**Dash branded products and services:** In addition to the above categories of personal data, Mapbox may also collect the following categories of personal data (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

‍

##### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data** 

Mapbox does not process personal data for the purposes of identifying an individual or creating or maintaining records about an individual. Instead, Mapbox processes personal data to:       

* Provide, test, maintain, secure and improve Mapbox products and services, 
* Provide customer requested support, including applying knowledge gained from individual customer support requests to benefit all Mapbox customers, to the extent such knowledge is de-identified,
* Prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks,
* Administer/bill customers (not end users),
* Calculate de-identified aggregate statistics,
* Train artificial intelligence models (to the extent personal data is first de-identified), which is a set of technologies and processes that allow computers to learn, reason, and assist in decision making; such models are used to improve Mapbox products and services,
* Anonymize such data so it is no longer considered personal data,
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations, and 
* Comply with applicable law.

Mapbox processes de-identified data only in a de-identified form and does not permit attempts to re-identify such data or associate with a natural person.

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above uses of personal data, Mapbox may also use personal data in the following ways (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Mapbox uses personal data for purposes that are compatible with those stated above such as providing and supporting the service. For Dash branded products and services, machine learning to develop and improve and fine tune Mapbox’s models is one of those purposes.
* Third party independent controller vendors will process the data you provide to Dash branded products and services for their own purposes. For more information visit their respective privacy policies (linked in Section 3). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

##### **To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**  

**Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to process in accordance  with Section 2 above.
* In response to a request, so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its customers or their end users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or due diligence related thereto of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

**Dash branded products and services:** In addition to the above parties that Mapbox may disclose personal data to, Mapbox may also disclose personal data to the following third party independent controllers (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Certain functionality to instruct Dash branded products and services to process a question such as when the end user says “hey Dash” or touches the Dash branded products and services icon or starts typing a command. PicoVoice’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://picovoice.ai/docs/privacy-policy/  (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* On-device speech-to-text (“STT”) vendor (which Mapbox has no control over and is selected by the end user based on their device) will transpose audio speech spoken to Dash branded products and services to a string of text and send it to Mapbox servers to answer the end users question. The on-device STT processing is subject to its respective published privacy practices, which you should review. Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Large language model providers (“LLMs”), such as OpenAI review the end users voice input text and formulate a response to the end user. OpenAI’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://openai.com/policies/privacy-policy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Text-to-speech (“TTS”) vendors, such as Eleven labs transform the Mapbox appended LLM response to an audio MP3 file that is spoken (in audio form) to the requestor via Dash branded products and services. ElevenLabs processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://elevenlabs.io/privacy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍**Data Retention**

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as Mapbox determines it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 above. In determining how long to retain personal data, Mapbox considers the amount, nature and sensitivity of the data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data, the purposes for which personal data is processed, applicable legal requirements, and Mapbox’s legitimate interests. The purposes for which Mapbox processes data may dictate different retention periods for the same types of data. For example, Mapbox retains IP addresses for 30 days and after such time, in select instances, may need to extend such retention period for an investigation based on its legitimate interests to secure its products and services, prevent fraud and for legal compliance purposes.

### **Changes to this Product Privacy Policy**

Mapbox will update this product privacy policy at its own discretion from time to time to reflect changes in Mapbox’s practices, technologies, legal requirements, and other factors. 

### **Contact Mapbox** 

Mapbox would love to hear any questions, concerns, or feedback about this product privacy policy or Mapbox’s data protection practices. Please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com.

Heading 1
=========

Heading 2
---------

### Heading 3

#### Heading 4

##### Heading 5

###### Heading 6

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur.

> Block quote

Ordered list

1. Item 1
2. Item 2
3. Item 3

Unordered list

* Item A
* Item B
* Item C

**Bold text**

_Emphasis_

Superscript

Subscript

Privacy & Security FAQ
----------------------

Last Updated:  Aug 22, 2023

1\. What is Mapbox?

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

13\. More questions?

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

### Want to receive updates on our sub-processors?

Please subscribe below:

Stay tuned for updates!

Please enter an email address that includes @.

‍**Mapbox Privacy Policies**
============================

* ‍[Privacy Policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)
* ‍[Product Privacy Policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy)

[**‍**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy)**California Notices At Collection**

* ‍[Privacy Policy "California Notice At Collection"](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#[AIFCAIFC])

Privacy Policy
--------------

This privacy policy describes the personal data Mapbox and/or its affiliates (hereinafter collectively referred to as “Mapbox”) may receive and why such personal data may be received in its capacity as a data controller, how such personal data may be used (including whom it may be shared with and for what purposes), and choices about such personal data.    

This privacy policy applies to the extent Mapbox processes personal data in its capacity as a data controller under the GDPR (or “business” under the CCPA) when an individual: (a) visits and engages with any of Mapbox’s websites, (b) attends a virtual or in-person Mapbox event, (c) provides contact information for the purposes of Mapbox contacting about Mapbox products/services, (d) uses third-party websites or applications that cite this privacy policy, (e) provide billing information for Mapbox products/services account administration, or (f) apply to or are contacted about possible employment with Mapbox. Personal data is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household, as defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.100 et seq. and its implementing regulations (“CCPA”), or relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (hereinafter referred to as "personal data").

This Privacy Policy does not apply when Mapbox acts as a data processor.  Most Mapbox customer personal data is not governed by this policy. Mapbox operates in the capacity of a data processor for certain personal data when operating Mapbox’s  products/services that are purchased by developers and businesses to develop their own licensed applications. As such, customers/prospective customers should read Mapbox’s data processing addendum (“DPA”): [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa) which governs certain customer personal data that may be processed through use of Mapbox products/services including creation of a Mapbox products/services account. For other data not Processed by Mapbox as a Processor, e.g. billing and usage statistics data, see [**Mapbox's Product Privacy Policy**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy).

Corporate Accounts: If any account created with Mapbox lists a corporate email address for a company with which an individual is currently (or was formerly) employed (a “Corporate Email”), then the corporate entity to whom the Corporate Email pertains is responsible for privacy practices relating to use of Corporate Email. If Corporate Email is used within the scope of this privacy policy (as described at the top of this privacy policy), then this privacy policy applies.  For clarification, commonly known personal email account services (e.g., Gmail, Yahoo, Outlook) are not Corporate Email.  

### **Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**     

* **‍**Identifiers: Such as, name, address, email, phone number, Mapbox account username.
* Commercial information: Such as, transaction data including billing contact’s name, work phone number, work email, work address, professional title, and company name. 
* Financial data: Such as, credit card data is _not_ processed by Mapbox. Instead, credit card data is processed by Stripe, a third-party PCI-certified payment service provider, in accordance with its [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
* Internet or other network or device activity: When visiting any Mapbox websites, Mapbox automatically receives certain information such as: (a) browser and device type, (b) operating system, and (c) referring web pages including the pages visited on such sites. And information such as, IP address, data collected via strictly necessary and accepted website cookies / similar technologies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website, settings, and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* Employment data: Such as, education and employment history and other relevant personal data provided in an employment application submitted to Mapbox, information from a background check including information provided from reference checks.
* Location information: Such as, the location of an event where an individual signed up to receive communication or interact with Mapbox.
* User-generated content: Such as, a public comment provided by an individual in a Mapbox hosted webinar, Mapbox blog, or like Mapbox forum. For avoidance of doubt, an individual’s Mapbox product/service feedback does not constitute user-generated content. 
* Inference data about an individual: Such as, services Mapbox thinks an individual may be interested in based on prior purchases or website browsing, subject to the [Mapbox cookie policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 
* Other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with an individual: Such as, contents of correspondence with: 1) a Mapbox service provider in order to bill for items that may have been shipped upon an individual’s request as a result of the individual’s engagement with a Mapbox marketing campaign in person or virtually. 2) Mapbox, whether received through a form submitted on its website, conversation (in person, virtual, or phone call) with its staff, or via an email sent to an \[at\]mapbox email account. 3) And such as, personal data from entities who provide personal data about individuals, their job functions, and the companies they work for. Such entities attests to Mapbox that they have obtained all necessary consents and have lawful grounds to share such personal data with Mapbox.

### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data**      

##### **Mapbox uses personal data to:**       

* Provide, test, maintain/support, secure and improve Mapbox’s websites, to prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks, to calculate de-identified aggregate statistics, and for account administration/ billing purposes. 
* Send marketing information, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications (e.g., marketing newsletters, telemarketing calls, SMS or push notifications, information about Mapbox products, news or events) about Mapbox, its affiliates and partners.
* Plan or host virtual or in person events, contests, or other programs.
* Create and manage the recruitment system, job applications and a database of interested individuals and leads (including verifying the information provided to Mapbox) and assess and evaluate applicants skills and qualifications against the position(s) applied for.
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations.  
* Comply with applicable law.

### ‍**To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**    

##### **Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to provide any of the services, or related services to those, outlined in Section 2 of this privacy policy. However, prior to sharing personal data with such parties, Mapbox will have a written agreement consistent with the obligations outlined in applicable data protection laws and regulations.                                                                           
* Advertising and analytics partners. Any secondary use or sharing of personal data obtained through the use of third party cookies by these third parties is subject to their respective privacy policies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* In response to a request so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

### ‍**International Transfers**

Personal data may be processed by one or more Mapbox affiliates, processors, or service providers in order to operate Mapbox’s business – for example, in the United States for account administration and billing. Therefore, personal data may be processed outside of the location from which it was received. Mapbox ensures that the transfer of personal data offers an adequate level of protection and security, for instance by entering into the appropriate agreements that continuously ensure the same level of protective measures as set forth in applicable data protection laws and regulations and certification certification under the EU-US Data Privacy Framework, UK Extension to the EU-US Data Privacy Framework, and the Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework (collectively, the “Data Privacy Framework” or “DPF”), and, if required, standard contractual clauses or alternative mechanism for the transfer of data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR) or other applicable regulators or legislators. 

Mapbox’s Notice of Certification under the DPF, is available here: [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification)

##### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR INDIVIDUALS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

##### **4.1 Legal bases for processing personal data:** 

Some countries require that companies only process personal data if they have a “legal basis” (or justifiable need) to process personal data. To the extent those laws apply, Mapbox’s legal bases to process personal data are as follows:

* To comply with a legal obligation to which Mapbox, as a controller, is subject.
* To protect the vital interests of an individual or of another natural person.
* For the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Mapbox as the controller or by an independent third party controller, except where the individual’s interests or fundamental rights and freedoms override such interests.
* Performance of the contract.
* Consent.

In all cases of data processing on the basis of legitimate interests, Mapbox considers the impact on the rights and freedoms of the individuals whose data may be part of the processing, and ensures that its processing activities do not contradict or place at unreasonable risk any such rights or freedoms. Mapbox has assessed that these legitimate interests are not overridden by the data protection interests or fundamental rights of any individuals. In all cases, Mapbox ensures that such processing is legal, fair, and reasonable. 

### **Retention** 

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 of this privacy policy.

### **Security**

Mapbox takes steps designed to secure personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.  Unfortunately, no system is 100% secure, and Mapbox cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal data it receives.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Mapbox does not accept liability for unintentional or accidental destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access.**‍**

### **Children**

Mapbox products/services, websites, events, and other communications are not intended or directed to children under the age of 18 (or other age of majority as required by local law), and Mapbox does not knowingly collect personal data from children. If the parent or legal guardian learns that their child has provided Mapbox with personal data without their consent, then they should contact Mapbox as set forth below in the Contact Mapbox section of this privacy policy. If Mapbox learns that it has collected personal data in violation of applicable law, it will promptly take steps to delete such personal data.

### **Choices About Personal Data**

An individual may opt-out of processing of their personal data within the scope of this privacy policy at any time and prevent further Mapbox processing by contacting Mapbox as described below. 

* **Email and Telephone Communications:**

Click the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email received from Mapbox to opt out of receiving future commercial emails. Note that for current customers, Mapbox will continue to send non-promotional communications which may not be opted out of (e.g., communications regarding products/services or updates to Mapbox Terms or this privacy policy). Mapbox processes requests to be placed on do-not-mail, do-not-phone, and do-not-contact lists as required by applicable law.

* **Website logs and cookies:**

Devices have settings to delete stored cookies and most browsers have the option to decline cookies. However, certain parts of Mapbox’s website (including pages that require login) will not be accessible if Mapbox cookies (first party cookies) are not accepted. In contrast, third-party cookies set by third parties for marketing and analytics purposes on Mapbox’s website can be disabled, in principle, without affecting access. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit the Mapbox website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 

* **In accordance with applicable law, the individual to whom the personal data pertains may have the following rights regarding their personal data:**

* Access/view personal data  
* Portability of personal data in a commonly machine readable format 
* Correct personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete
* Deletion of personal data
* Restrict or object to processing of personal data
* Opt-out of the sale of personal data, if applicable, where such requests are permitted by law and as defined in the CCPA.

To exercise your right to deletion of personal data, please complete the form [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/ccpa-deletion-request#:~:text=To%20delete%20account%2Drelated%20information,you%20believe%20Mapbox%20obtained%20it.). For any other rights, please contact Mapbox at [privacy@mapbox.com](mailto:privacy@mapbox.com). In your email include  name, and request or question. To protect privacy, Mapbox will take steps to verify the identity of the requestor before fulfilling the request. Mapbox will process such requests in accordance with applicable laws. Although we encourage you to contact us if you have questions or complaints, you also have the right to lodge a complaint in the EU and UK with the appropriate supervisory authority in your jurisdiction. In some cases, these rights may be subject to exceptions, as permitted by applicable law. 

### **Additional Information For California Residents**

##### **9.1 California Notice At Collection:**

**Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**

* **‍**Identifiers: Such as, name, address, email, phone number, Mapbox account username.
* Commercial information: Such as, transaction data including billing contact’s name, work phone number, work email, work address, professional title, and company name. 
* Financial data: Such as, credit card data is _not_ processed by Mapbox. Instead, credit card data is processed by Stripe, a third-party PCI-certified payment service provider, in accordance with its [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
* Internet or other network or device activity: When visiting any Mapbox websites, Mapbox automatically receives certain information such as: (a) browser and device type, (b) operating system, and (c) referring web pages including the pages visited on such sites. And information such as, IP address, data collected via strictly necessary and accepted website cookies / similar technologies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website, settings, and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* Employment data: Such as, education and employment history and other relevant personal data provided in an employment application submitted to Mapbox, information from a background check including information provided from reference checks.
* Location information: Such as, the location of an event where an individual signed up to receive communication or interact with Mapbox.
* User-generated content: Such as, a public comment provided by an individual in a Mapbox hosted webinar, Mapbox blog, or like Mapbox forum. For avoidance of doubt, an individual’s Mapbox product/service feedback does not constitute user-generated content. 
* Inference data about an individual: Such as, services Mapbox thinks an individual may be interested in based on prior purchases or website browsing, subject to the [Mapbox cookie policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 
* Other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with an individual: Such as, contents of correspondence with: 1) a Mapbox service provider in order to bill for items that may have been shipped upon an individual’s request as a result of the individual’s engagement with a Mapbox marketing campaign in person or virtually. 2) Mapbox, whether received through a form submitted on its website, conversation (in person, virtual, or phone call) with its staff, or via an email sent to an \[at\]mapbox email account. 3) And such as, personal data from entities who provide personal data about individuals, their job functions, and the companies they work for. Such entities attests to Mapbox that they have obtained all necessary consents and have lawful grounds to share such personal data with Mapbox.

**How Mapbox Uses Personal Data** 

* Provide, test, maintain/support, secure and improve Mapbox’s websites, to prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks, to calculate de-identified aggregate statistics, and for account administration/ billing purposes. 
* Send marketing information, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications (e.g., marketing newsletters, telemarketing calls, SMS or push notifications, information about Mapbox products, news or events) about Mapbox, its affiliates and partners.
* Plan or host virtual or in person events, contests, or other programs.
* Create and manage the recruitment system, job applications and a database of interested individuals and leads (including verifying the information provided to Mapbox) and assess and evaluate applicants skills and qualifications against the position(s) applied for.
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations.  
* Comply with applicable law.

**To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**  

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to provide any of the services, or related services to those, outlined in Section 2 of this privacy policy. However, prior to sharing personal data with such parties, Mapbox will have a written agreement consistent with the obligations outlined in applicable data protection laws and regulations.                                                                           
* Advertising and analytics partners. Any secondary use or sharing of personal data obtained through the use of third party cookies by these third parties is subject to their respective privacy policies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* In response to a request so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

**Data Retention**

* Only for so long as Mapbox has a business purpose to retain and process such personal data.                                                      

### **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

Mapbox will update this privacy policy at its own discretion from time to time to reflect changes in Mapbox’s practices, technologies, legal requirements, and other factors. **‍**

### **Contact Mapbox** 

Mapbox would love to hear any questions, concerns, or feedback about this privacy policy or Mapbox’s data protection practices. Please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com.

* * *

**Mapbox Product Privacy Policy**
---------------------------------

**See Section 9 below for "California Notice At Collection"**

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers map and location services in a wide variety of web, mobile, game and embedded device applications. Mapbox customers are developers/companies who embed Mapbox software development kits (SDKs) or integrate with Mapbox application program interfaces (APIs) (collectively, “**Mapbox materials**”) in their licensed applications to enable maps and location features.  

**This product privacy policy** applies when Mapbox is processing personal data (sometimes referred to as personal information), from an end user of a licensed application (provided by Mapbox or one of its customers) that contains Mapbox materials, in its capacity (where legally applicable) as an independent data controller. For example, when Mapbox determines the purpose and means of processing such as making decisions about how to process personal data that benefits Mapbox customers generally, not just a single customer, Mapbox is processing as an independent data controller. In all cases, Mapbox’s processing of personal data continues to be controlled by its contracts with Mapbox customers, this product privacy policy and applicable data protection laws and regulations. 

Personal data is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, or relating to an identified or identifiable natural person, or data defined as personal information or personal data under applicable data protection laws and regulations (in this policy, referred to as "**personal data**”).

**Additional Privacy Policy:** Mapbox also processes as a data controller when individuals use any Mapbox website or engage with Mapbox marketing programs, including attending live or virtual events or applying for a job with Mapbox. Please see the applicable Mapbox privacy policy, available [here.](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)

### Personal Data Mapbox May Receive

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to its product development and operations in an effort to collect the least amount of personal data from the outset. The limited personal dataset that Mapbox may receive, outlined below, describes personal data categories and associated example data elements.  Please note, many data elements are only classified as personal data when combined with an associated IP address, other persistent identifier or data element capable of identifying or being reasonably linked to a natural person.

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

‍

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above categories of personal data, Mapbox may also collect the following categories of personal data (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

‍

### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data**

Mapbox does not process personal data for the purposes of identifying an individual or creating or maintaining records about an individual. Instead, Mapbox processes personal data to:       

* Provide, test, maintain, secure and improve Mapbox products and services, 
* Provide customer requested support, including applying knowledge gained from individual customer support requests to benefit all Mapbox customers, to the extent such knowledge is de-identified,
* Prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks,
* Administer/bill customers (not end users),
* Calculate de-identified aggregate statistics,
* Train artificial intelligence models (to the extent personal data is first de-identified), which is a set of technologies and processes that allow computers to learn, reason, and assist in decision making; such models are used to improve Mapbox products and services,
* Anonymize such data so it is no longer considered personal data,
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations, and 
* Comply with applicable law.

Mapbox processes de-identified data only in a de-identified form and does not permit attempts to re-identify such data or associate with a natural person.

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above uses of personal data, Mapbox may also use personal data in the following ways (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Mapbox uses personal data for purposes that are compatible with those stated above such as providing and supporting the service. For Dash branded products and services, machine learning to develop and improve and fine tune Mapbox’s models is one of those purposes.
* Third party independent controller vendors will process the data you provide to Dash branded products and services for their own purposes. For more information visit their respective privacy policies (linked in Section 3). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍

### **To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data** 

**Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to process in accordance  with Section 2 above. 
* In response to a request, so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its customers or their end users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or due diligence related thereto of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

Dash branded products and services: In addition to the above parties that Mapbox may disclose personal data to, Mapbox may also disclose personal data to the following third party independent controllers (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Certain functionality to instruct Dash branded products and services to process a question such as when the end user says “hey Dash” or touches the Dash branded products and services icon or starts typing a command. PicoVoice’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://picovoice.ai/docs/privacy-policy/  (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* On-device speech-to-text (“STT”) vendor (which Mapbox has no control over and is selected by the end user based on their device) will transpose audio speech spoken to Dash branded products and services to a string of text and send it to Mapbox servers to answer the end users question. The on-device STT processing is subject to its respective published privacy practices, which you should review. Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Large language model providers (“LLMs”), such as OpenAI review the end users voice input text and formulate a response to the end user. OpenAI’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://openai.com/policies/privacy-policy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Text-to-speech (“TTS”) vendors, such as Eleven labs transform the Mapbox appended LLM response to an audio MP3 file that is spoken (in audio form) to the requestor via Dash branded products and services. ElevenLabs processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://elevenlabs.io/privacy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍

### **International Transfers**

Personal data may be processed by one or more Mapbox affiliates, processors, or service providers in order to operate Mapbox’s business – for example, in the United States for account administration and billing. Therefore, personal data may be processed outside of the location from which it was received. Mapbox ensures that the transfer of personal data offers an adequate level of protection and security, for instance by entering into the appropriate agreements that continuously ensure the same level of protective measures as set forth in applicable data protection laws and regulations and certification certification under the EU-US, UK-US, Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework ("DPF"), and, if required, standard contractual clauses or alternative mechanism for the transfer of data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR) or other applicable regulators or legislators. 

Mapbox’s Notice of Certification under the DPF, is available here: [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification)

##### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR INDIVIDUALS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

##### **4.1 Legal bases for processing personal data:** 

Some countries require that companies only process personal data if they have a “legal basis” (or justifiable need) to process personal data. To the extent those laws apply, Mapbox’s legal bases to process personal data are as follows:

* To comply with a legal obligation to which Mapbox, as a controller, is subject.
* To protect the vital interests of an individual or of another natural person.
* For the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Mapbox as the controller or by an independent third party controller, except where the individual’s interests or fundamental rights and freedoms override such interests.
* Performance of the contract.
* Consent.

In all cases of data processing on the basis of legitimate interests, Mapbox considers the impact on the rights and freedoms of the individuals whose data may be part of the processing, and ensures that its processing activities do not contradict or place at unreasonable risk any such rights or freedoms. Mapbox has assessed that these legitimate interests are not overridden by the data protection interests or fundamental rights of any individuals. In all cases, Mapbox ensures that such processing is legal, fair, and reasonable. 

### **Retention** 

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as Mapbox determines it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 above. In determining how long to retain personal data, Mapbox considers the amount, nature and sensitivity of the data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data, the purposes for which personal data is processed, applicable legal requirements, and Mapbox’s legitimate interests. The purposes for which Mapbox processes data may dictate different retention periods for the same types of data. For example, Mapbox retains IP addresses for 30 days and after such time, in select instances, may need to extend such retention period for an investigation based on its legitimate interests to secure its products and services, prevent fraud and for legal compliance purposes.

### **Security**

Mapbox takes steps designed to secure personal data in accordance with this product privacy policy.  Unfortunately, no system is 100% secure, and Mapbox cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal data it receives.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Mapbox does not accept liability for unintentional or accidental destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access.

### **Children**

Mapbox products and services are not intended or directed to children under the age of 18 (or other age of majority as required by local law), and Mapbox does not knowingly collect personal data from children. If the parent or legal guardian learns that their child has provided Mapbox with personal data without their consent, then they should contact Mapbox as set forth below in the Contact Mapbox section of this product privacy policy. If Mapbox learns that it has collected personal data in violation of applicable data protection laws and regulations, it will promptly take steps to delete such personal data.

### **Choices About Personal Data** 

To the fullest extent possible, Mapbox will fulfill data subject rights requests provided it can match a data subject (natural person to whom the personal data in question pertains) to personal data that Mapbox processes. Mapbox does not, and is not required to, collect additional personal data in order to positively identify a data subject. 

As outlined in Section 1 above, Mapbox receives only minimal personal data and operates controls designed to promptly de-identify and anonymize such personal data. For example, Mapbox deletes IP addresses within 30 days of receipt (unless required for an investigation), so it is unlikely that Mapbox would have personal data capable of identifying a data subject after 30 days of receiving such data. However, if verifiable and detailed information is available, Mapbox will work with the data subject to determine if the request can reasonably be met. The data subject will need to provide a valid email address so that Mapbox can communicate and support the request, as well as any information that Mapbox determines may be needed to verify whether it holds any applicable personal data. 

**In accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations and depending upon the data subject’s residency, the data subject to whom the personal data pertains may have the right to request the following regarding certain of their personal data:**

* Access/view/know personal data  
* Portability of personal data in a commonly machine readable format 
* Correct personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete
* Deletion of certain personal data
* Restrict or object to processing of personal data
* Opt-out of the “sale” or “share” or processing for “targeted advertising” (each as defined by applicable data protection laws and regulations) of personal data , if applicable, where such requests are permitted by law

To request deletion of certain personal data, please complete the form [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/ccpa-deletion-request#:~:text=To%20delete%20account%2Drelated%20information,you%20believe%20Mapbox%20obtained%20it.). For any other request to exercise rights, please contact Mapbox at [privacy@mapbox.com](mailto:privacy@mapbox.com). The requesting email must come from the data subject to whom the personal data pertains and include the data subject’s name, email address and specific request or question. To protect privacy, Mapbox will take steps to verify the identity of the requestor before fulfilling the request. Mapbox will process such requests in accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations. 

To the extent required in the state where the data subject resides and where Mapbox has denied such data subject’s earlier request, the data subject may file an appeal with Mapbox for reconsideration. To file an appeal, please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com. The requesting email must come from the data subject to whom the personal data pertains and include the data subject’s name, email address and reference to the specific request and denial.

Mapbox encourages data subjects to contact it directly with any questions or complaints. However, Mapbox acknowledges and informs the data subject that they have the right to lodge a complaint in the EU and UK with the appropriate supervisory authority in the applicable jurisdiction; .; and in select United States states, to contact the respective state’s Attorney General’s Office, whose contact information may be identified here https://www.usa.gov/state-attorney-general (or successor link). In some cases, these rights may be subject to exceptions, as permitted by applicable law.

### **Additional Information For California Residents**

##### **9.1 California Notice At Collection:**

**Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to its product development and operations in an effort to collect the least amount of personal data from the outset. The limited personal dataset that Mapbox may receive, outlined below, describes personal data categories and associated example data elements.  Please note, many data elements are only classified as personal data when combined with an associated IP address, other persistent identifier or data element capable of identifying or being reasonably linked to a natural person.

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s company name (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name. |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(an IP address is not associated with such geolocation data and the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

‍

**Dash branded products and services:** In addition to the above categories of personal data, Mapbox may also collect the following categories of personal data (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

‍

##### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data** 

Mapbox does not process personal data for the purposes of identifying an individual or creating or maintaining records about an individual. Instead, Mapbox processes personal data to:       

* Provide, test, maintain, secure and improve Mapbox products and services, 
* Provide customer requested support, including applying knowledge gained from individual customer support requests to benefit all Mapbox customers, to the extent such knowledge is de-identified,
* Prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks,
* Administer/bill customers (not end users),
* Calculate de-identified aggregate statistics,
* Train artificial intelligence models (to the extent personal data is first de-identified), which is a set of technologies and processes that allow computers to learn, reason, and assist in decision making; such models are used to improve Mapbox products and services,
* Anonymize such data so it is no longer considered personal data,
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations, and 
* Comply with applicable law.

Mapbox processes de-identified data only in a de-identified form and does not permit attempts to re-identify such data or associate with a natural person.

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above uses of personal data, Mapbox may also use personal data in the following ways (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Mapbox uses personal data for purposes that are compatible with those stated above such as providing and supporting the service. For Dash branded products and services, machine learning to develop and improve and fine tune Mapbox’s models is one of those purposes.
* Third party independent controller vendors will process the data you provide to Dash branded products and services for their own purposes. For more information visit their respective privacy policies (linked in Section 3). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

##### **To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**  

**Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to process in accordance  with Section 2 above.
* In response to a request, so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its customers or their end users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or due diligence related thereto of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

**Dash branded products and services:** In addition to the above parties that Mapbox may disclose personal data to, Mapbox may also disclose personal data to the following third party independent controllers (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Certain functionality to instruct Dash branded products and services to process a question such as when the end user says “hey Dash” or touches the Dash branded products and services icon or starts typing a command. PicoVoice’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://picovoice.ai/docs/privacy-policy/  (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* On-device speech-to-text (“STT”) vendor (which Mapbox has no control over and is selected by the end user based on their device) will transpose audio speech spoken to Dash branded products and services to a string of text and send it to Mapbox servers to answer the end users question. The on-device STT processing is subject to its respective published privacy practices, which you should review. Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Large language model providers (“LLMs”), such as OpenAI review the end users voice input text and formulate a response to the end user. OpenAI’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://openai.com/policies/privacy-policy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Text-to-speech (“TTS”) vendors, such as Eleven labs transform the Mapbox appended LLM response to an audio MP3 file that is spoken (in audio form) to the requestor via Dash branded products and services. ElevenLabs processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://elevenlabs.io/privacy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍**Data Retention**

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as Mapbox determines it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 above. In determining how long to retain personal data, Mapbox considers the amount, nature and sensitivity of the data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data, the purposes for which personal data is processed, applicable legal requirements, and Mapbox’s legitimate interests. The purposes for which Mapbox processes data may dictate different retention periods for the same types of data. For example, Mapbox retains IP addresses for 30 days and after such time, in select instances, may need to extend such retention period for an investigation based on its legitimate interests to secure its products and services, prevent fraud and for legal compliance purposes.

### **Changes to this Product Privacy Policy**

Mapbox will update this product privacy policy at its own discretion from time to time to reflect changes in Mapbox’s practices, technologies, legal requirements, and other factors. 

### **Contact Mapbox** 

Mapbox would love to hear any questions, concerns, or feedback about this product privacy policy or Mapbox’s data protection practices. Please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com.

Heading 1
=========

Heading 2
---------

### Heading 3

#### Heading 4

##### Heading 5

###### Heading 6

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur.

> Block quote

Ordered list

1. Item 1
2. Item 2
3. Item 3

Unordered list

* Item A
* Item B
* Item C

**Bold text**

_Emphasis_

Superscript

Subscript

Privacy & Security FAQ
----------------------

Last Updated:  Aug 22, 2023

1\. What is Mapbox?

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

13\. More questions?

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

### Want to receive updates on our sub-processors?

Please subscribe below:

Stay tuned for updates!

Please enter an email address that includes @.

‍**Mapbox Privacy Policies**
============================

* ‍[Privacy Policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)
* ‍[Product Privacy Policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy)

[**‍**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy)**California Notices At Collection**

* ‍[Privacy Policy "California Notice At Collection"](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#[AIFCAIFC])

Privacy Policy
--------------

This privacy policy describes the personal data Mapbox and/or its affiliates (hereinafter collectively referred to as “Mapbox”) may receive and why such personal data may be received in its capacity as a data controller, how such personal data may be used (including whom it may be shared with and for what purposes), and choices about such personal data.    

This privacy policy applies to the extent Mapbox processes personal data in its capacity as a data controller under the GDPR (or “business” under the CCPA) when an individual: (a) visits and engages with any of Mapbox’s websites, (b) attends a virtual or in-person Mapbox event, (c) provides contact information for the purposes of Mapbox contacting about Mapbox products/services, (d) uses third-party websites or applications that cite this privacy policy, (e) provide billing information for Mapbox products/services account administration, or (f) apply to or are contacted about possible employment with Mapbox. Personal data is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household, as defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.100 et seq. and its implementing regulations (“CCPA”), or relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (hereinafter referred to as "personal data").

This Privacy Policy does not apply when Mapbox acts as a data processor.  Most Mapbox customer personal data is not governed by this policy. Mapbox operates in the capacity of a data processor for certain personal data when operating Mapbox’s  products/services that are purchased by developers and businesses to develop their own licensed applications. As such, customers/prospective customers should read Mapbox’s data processing addendum (“DPA”): [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa) which governs certain customer personal data that may be processed through use of Mapbox products/services including creation of a Mapbox products/services account. For other data not Processed by Mapbox as a Processor, e.g. billing and usage statistics data, see [**Mapbox's Product Privacy Policy**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy).

Corporate Accounts: If any account created with Mapbox lists a corporate email address for a company with which an individual is currently (or was formerly) employed (a “Corporate Email”), then the corporate entity to whom the Corporate Email pertains is responsible for privacy practices relating to use of Corporate Email. If Corporate Email is used within the scope of this privacy policy (as described at the top of this privacy policy), then this privacy policy applies.  For clarification, commonly known personal email account services (e.g., Gmail, Yahoo, Outlook) are not Corporate Email.  

### **Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**     

* **‍**Identifiers: Such as, name, address, email, phone number, Mapbox account username.
* Commercial information: Such as, transaction data including billing contact’s name, work phone number, work email, work address, professional title, and company name. 
* Financial data: Such as, credit card data is _not_ processed by Mapbox. Instead, credit card data is processed by Stripe, a third-party PCI-certified payment service provider, in accordance with its [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
* Internet or other network or device activity: When visiting any Mapbox websites, Mapbox automatically receives certain information such as: (a) browser and device type, (b) operating system, and (c) referring web pages including the pages visited on such sites. And information such as, IP address, data collected via strictly necessary and accepted website cookies / similar technologies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website, settings, and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* Employment data: Such as, education and employment history and other relevant personal data provided in an employment application submitted to Mapbox, information from a background check including information provided from reference checks.
* Location information: Such as, the location of an event where an individual signed up to receive communication or interact with Mapbox.
* User-generated content: Such as, a public comment provided by an individual in a Mapbox hosted webinar, Mapbox blog, or like Mapbox forum. For avoidance of doubt, an individual’s Mapbox product/service feedback does not constitute user-generated content. 
* Inference data about an individual: Such as, services Mapbox thinks an individual may be interested in based on prior purchases or website browsing, subject to the [Mapbox cookie policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 
* Other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with an individual: Such as, contents of correspondence with: 1) a Mapbox service provider in order to bill for items that may have been shipped upon an individual’s request as a result of the individual’s engagement with a Mapbox marketing campaign in person or virtually. 2) Mapbox, whether received through a form submitted on its website, conversation (in person, virtual, or phone call) with its staff, or via an email sent to an \[at\]mapbox email account. 3) And such as, personal data from entities who provide personal data about individuals, their job functions, and the companies they work for. Such entities attests to Mapbox that they have obtained all necessary consents and have lawful grounds to share such personal data with Mapbox.

### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data**      

##### **Mapbox uses personal data to:**       

* Provide, test, maintain/support, secure and improve Mapbox’s websites, to prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks, to calculate de-identified aggregate statistics, and for account administration/ billing purposes. 
* Send marketing information, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications (e.g., marketing newsletters, telemarketing calls, SMS or push notifications, information about Mapbox products, news or events) about Mapbox, its affiliates and partners.
* Plan or host virtual or in person events, contests, or other programs.
* Create and manage the recruitment system, job applications and a database of interested individuals and leads (including verifying the information provided to Mapbox) and assess and evaluate applicants skills and qualifications against the position(s) applied for.
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations.  
* Comply with applicable law.

### ‍**To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**    

##### **Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to provide any of the services, or related services to those, outlined in Section 2 of this privacy policy. However, prior to sharing personal data with such parties, Mapbox will have a written agreement consistent with the obligations outlined in applicable data protection laws and regulations.                                                                           
* Advertising and analytics partners. Any secondary use or sharing of personal data obtained through the use of third party cookies by these third parties is subject to their respective privacy policies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* In response to a request so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

### ‍**International Transfers**

Personal data may be processed by one or more Mapbox affiliates, processors, or service providers in order to operate Mapbox’s business – for example, in the United States for account administration and billing. Therefore, personal data may be processed outside of the location from which it was received. Mapbox ensures that the transfer of personal data offers an adequate level of protection and security, for instance by entering into the appropriate agreements that continuously ensure the same level of protective measures as set forth in applicable data protection laws and regulations and certification certification under the EU-US Data Privacy Framework, UK Extension to the EU-US Data Privacy Framework, and the Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework (collectively, the “Data Privacy Framework” or “DPF”), and, if required, standard contractual clauses or alternative mechanism for the transfer of data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR) or other applicable regulators or legislators. 

Mapbox’s Notice of Certification under the DPF, is available here: [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification)

##### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR INDIVIDUALS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

##### **4.1 Legal bases for processing personal data:** 

Some countries require that companies only process personal data if they have a “legal basis” (or justifiable need) to process personal data. To the extent those laws apply, Mapbox’s legal bases to process personal data are as follows:

* To comply with a legal obligation to which Mapbox, as a controller, is subject.
* To protect the vital interests of an individual or of another natural person.
* For the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Mapbox as the controller or by an independent third party controller, except where the individual’s interests or fundamental rights and freedoms override such interests.
* Performance of the contract.
* Consent.

In all cases of data processing on the basis of legitimate interests, Mapbox considers the impact on the rights and freedoms of the individuals whose data may be part of the processing, and ensures that its processing activities do not contradict or place at unreasonable risk any such rights or freedoms. Mapbox has assessed that these legitimate interests are not overridden by the data protection interests or fundamental rights of any individuals. In all cases, Mapbox ensures that such processing is legal, fair, and reasonable. 

### **Retention** 

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 of this privacy policy.

### **Security**

Mapbox takes steps designed to secure personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.  Unfortunately, no system is 100% secure, and Mapbox cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal data it receives.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Mapbox does not accept liability for unintentional or accidental destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access.**‍**

### **Children**

Mapbox products/services, websites, events, and other communications are not intended or directed to children under the age of 18 (or other age of majority as required by local law), and Mapbox does not knowingly collect personal data from children. If the parent or legal guardian learns that their child has provided Mapbox with personal data without their consent, then they should contact Mapbox as set forth below in the Contact Mapbox section of this privacy policy. If Mapbox learns that it has collected personal data in violation of applicable law, it will promptly take steps to delete such personal data.

### **Choices About Personal Data**

An individual may opt-out of processing of their personal data within the scope of this privacy policy at any time and prevent further Mapbox processing by contacting Mapbox as described below. 

* **Email and Telephone Communications:**

Click the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email received from Mapbox to opt out of receiving future commercial emails. Note that for current customers, Mapbox will continue to send non-promotional communications which may not be opted out of (e.g., communications regarding products/services or updates to Mapbox Terms or this privacy policy). Mapbox processes requests to be placed on do-not-mail, do-not-phone, and do-not-contact lists as required by applicable law.

* **Website logs and cookies:**

Devices have settings to delete stored cookies and most browsers have the option to decline cookies. However, certain parts of Mapbox’s website (including pages that require login) will not be accessible if Mapbox cookies (first party cookies) are not accepted. In contrast, third-party cookies set by third parties for marketing and analytics purposes on Mapbox’s website can be disabled, in principle, without affecting access. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit the Mapbox website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 

* **In accordance with applicable law, the individual to whom the personal data pertains may have the following rights regarding their personal data:**

* Access/view personal data  
* Portability of personal data in a commonly machine readable format 
* Correct personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete
* Deletion of personal data
* Restrict or object to processing of personal data
* Opt-out of the sale of personal data, if applicable, where such requests are permitted by law and as defined in the CCPA.

To exercise your right to deletion of personal data, please complete the form [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/ccpa-deletion-request#:~:text=To%20delete%20account%2Drelated%20information,you%20believe%20Mapbox%20obtained%20it.). For any other rights, please contact Mapbox at [privacy@mapbox.com](mailto:privacy@mapbox.com). In your email include  name, and request or question. To protect privacy, Mapbox will take steps to verify the identity of the requestor before fulfilling the request. Mapbox will process such requests in accordance with applicable laws. Although we encourage you to contact us if you have questions or complaints, you also have the right to lodge a complaint in the EU and UK with the appropriate supervisory authority in your jurisdiction. In some cases, these rights may be subject to exceptions, as permitted by applicable law. 

### **Additional Information For California Residents**

##### **9.1 California Notice At Collection:**

**Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**

* **‍**Identifiers: Such as, name, address, email, phone number, Mapbox account username.
* Commercial information: Such as, transaction data including billing contact’s name, work phone number, work email, work address, professional title, and company name. 
* Financial data: Such as, credit card data is _not_ processed by Mapbox. Instead, credit card data is processed by Stripe, a third-party PCI-certified payment service provider, in accordance with its [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
* Internet or other network or device activity: When visiting any Mapbox websites, Mapbox automatically receives certain information such as: (a) browser and device type, (b) operating system, and (c) referring web pages including the pages visited on such sites. And information such as, IP address, data collected via strictly necessary and accepted website cookies / similar technologies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website, settings, and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* Employment data: Such as, education and employment history and other relevant personal data provided in an employment application submitted to Mapbox, information from a background check including information provided from reference checks.
* Location information: Such as, the location of an event where an individual signed up to receive communication or interact with Mapbox.
* User-generated content: Such as, a public comment provided by an individual in a Mapbox hosted webinar, Mapbox blog, or like Mapbox forum. For avoidance of doubt, an individual’s Mapbox product/service feedback does not constitute user-generated content. 
* Inference data about an individual: Such as, services Mapbox thinks an individual may be interested in based on prior purchases or website browsing, subject to the [Mapbox cookie policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 
* Other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with an individual: Such as, contents of correspondence with: 1) a Mapbox service provider in order to bill for items that may have been shipped upon an individual’s request as a result of the individual’s engagement with a Mapbox marketing campaign in person or virtually. 2) Mapbox, whether received through a form submitted on its website, conversation (in person, virtual, or phone call) with its staff, or via an email sent to an \[at\]mapbox email account. 3) And such as, personal data from entities who provide personal data about individuals, their job functions, and the companies they work for. Such entities attests to Mapbox that they have obtained all necessary consents and have lawful grounds to share such personal data with Mapbox.

**How Mapbox Uses Personal Data** 

* Provide, test, maintain/support, secure and improve Mapbox’s websites, to prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks, to calculate de-identified aggregate statistics, and for account administration/ billing purposes. 
* Send marketing information, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications (e.g., marketing newsletters, telemarketing calls, SMS or push notifications, information about Mapbox products, news or events) about Mapbox, its affiliates and partners.
* Plan or host virtual or in person events, contests, or other programs.
* Create and manage the recruitment system, job applications and a database of interested individuals and leads (including verifying the information provided to Mapbox) and assess and evaluate applicants skills and qualifications against the position(s) applied for.
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations.  
* Comply with applicable law.

**To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**  

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to provide any of the services, or related services to those, outlined in Section 2 of this privacy policy. However, prior to sharing personal data with such parties, Mapbox will have a written agreement consistent with the obligations outlined in applicable data protection laws and regulations.                                                                           
* Advertising and analytics partners. Any secondary use or sharing of personal data obtained through the use of third party cookies by these third parties is subject to their respective privacy policies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* In response to a request so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

**Data Retention**

* Only for so long as Mapbox has a business purpose to retain and process such personal data.                                                      

### **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

Mapbox will update this privacy policy at its own discretion from time to time to reflect changes in Mapbox’s practices, technologies, legal requirements, and other factors. **‍**

### **Contact Mapbox** 

Mapbox would love to hear any questions, concerns, or feedback about this privacy policy or Mapbox’s data protection practices. Please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com.

* * *

**Mapbox Product Privacy Policy**
---------------------------------

**See Section 9 below for "California Notice At Collection"**

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers map and location services in a wide variety of web, mobile, game and embedded device applications. Mapbox customers are developers/companies who embed Mapbox software development kits (SDKs) or integrate with Mapbox application program interfaces (APIs) (collectively, “**Mapbox materials**”) in their licensed applications to enable maps and location features.  

**This product privacy policy** applies when Mapbox is processing personal data (sometimes referred to as personal information), from an end user of a licensed application (provided by Mapbox or one of its customers) that contains Mapbox materials, in its capacity (where legally applicable) as an independent data controller. For example, when Mapbox determines the purpose and means of processing such as making decisions about how to process personal data that benefits Mapbox customers generally, not just a single customer, Mapbox is processing as an independent data controller. In all cases, Mapbox’s processing of personal data continues to be controlled by its contracts with Mapbox customers, this product privacy policy and applicable data protection laws and regulations. 

Personal data is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, or relating to an identified or identifiable natural person, or data defined as personal information or personal data under applicable data protection laws and regulations (in this policy, referred to as "**personal data**”).

**Additional Privacy Policy:** Mapbox also processes as a data controller when individuals use any Mapbox website or engage with Mapbox marketing programs, including attending live or virtual events or applying for a job with Mapbox. Please see the applicable Mapbox privacy policy, available [here.](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)

### Personal Data Mapbox May Receive

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to its product development and operations in an effort to collect the least amount of personal data from the outset. The limited personal dataset that Mapbox may receive, outlined below, describes personal data categories and associated example data elements.  Please note, many data elements are only classified as personal data when combined with an associated IP address, other persistent identifier or data element capable of identifying or being reasonably linked to a natural person.

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

‍

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above categories of personal data, Mapbox may also collect the following categories of personal data (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

‍

### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data**

Mapbox does not process personal data for the purposes of identifying an individual or creating or maintaining records about an individual. Instead, Mapbox processes personal data to:       

* Provide, test, maintain, secure and improve Mapbox products and services, 
* Provide customer requested support, including applying knowledge gained from individual customer support requests to benefit all Mapbox customers, to the extent such knowledge is de-identified,
* Prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks,
* Administer/bill customers (not end users),
* Calculate de-identified aggregate statistics,
* Train artificial intelligence models (to the extent personal data is first de-identified), which is a set of technologies and processes that allow computers to learn, reason, and assist in decision making; such models are used to improve Mapbox products and services,
* Anonymize such data so it is no longer considered personal data,
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations, and 
* Comply with applicable law.

Mapbox processes de-identified data only in a de-identified form and does not permit attempts to re-identify such data or associate with a natural person.

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above uses of personal data, Mapbox may also use personal data in the following ways (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Mapbox uses personal data for purposes that are compatible with those stated above such as providing and supporting the service. For Dash branded products and services, machine learning to develop and improve and fine tune Mapbox’s models is one of those purposes.
* Third party independent controller vendors will process the data you provide to Dash branded products and services for their own purposes. For more information visit their respective privacy policies (linked in Section 3). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍

### **To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data** 

**Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to process in accordance  with Section 2 above. 
* In response to a request, so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its customers or their end users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or due diligence related thereto of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

Dash branded products and services: In addition to the above parties that Mapbox may disclose personal data to, Mapbox may also disclose personal data to the following third party independent controllers (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Certain functionality to instruct Dash branded products and services to process a question such as when the end user says “hey Dash” or touches the Dash branded products and services icon or starts typing a command. PicoVoice’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://picovoice.ai/docs/privacy-policy/  (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* On-device speech-to-text (“STT”) vendor (which Mapbox has no control over and is selected by the end user based on their device) will transpose audio speech spoken to Dash branded products and services to a string of text and send it to Mapbox servers to answer the end users question. The on-device STT processing is subject to its respective published privacy practices, which you should review. Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Large language model providers (“LLMs”), such as OpenAI review the end users voice input text and formulate a response to the end user. OpenAI’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://openai.com/policies/privacy-policy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Text-to-speech (“TTS”) vendors, such as Eleven labs transform the Mapbox appended LLM response to an audio MP3 file that is spoken (in audio form) to the requestor via Dash branded products and services. ElevenLabs processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://elevenlabs.io/privacy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍

### **International Transfers**

Personal data may be processed by one or more Mapbox affiliates, processors, or service providers in order to operate Mapbox’s business – for example, in the United States for account administration and billing. Therefore, personal data may be processed outside of the location from which it was received. Mapbox ensures that the transfer of personal data offers an adequate level of protection and security, for instance by entering into the appropriate agreements that continuously ensure the same level of protective measures as set forth in applicable data protection laws and regulations and certification certification under the EU-US, UK-US, Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework ("DPF"), and, if required, standard contractual clauses or alternative mechanism for the transfer of data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR) or other applicable regulators or legislators. 

Mapbox’s Notice of Certification under the DPF, is available here: [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification)

##### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR INDIVIDUALS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

##### **4.1 Legal bases for processing personal data:** 

Some countries require that companies only process personal data if they have a “legal basis” (or justifiable need) to process personal data. To the extent those laws apply, Mapbox’s legal bases to process personal data are as follows:

* To comply with a legal obligation to which Mapbox, as a controller, is subject.
* To protect the vital interests of an individual or of another natural person.
* For the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Mapbox as the controller or by an independent third party controller, except where the individual’s interests or fundamental rights and freedoms override such interests.
* Performance of the contract.
* Consent.

In all cases of data processing on the basis of legitimate interests, Mapbox considers the impact on the rights and freedoms of the individuals whose data may be part of the processing, and ensures that its processing activities do not contradict or place at unreasonable risk any such rights or freedoms. Mapbox has assessed that these legitimate interests are not overridden by the data protection interests or fundamental rights of any individuals. In all cases, Mapbox ensures that such processing is legal, fair, and reasonable. 

### **Retention** 

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as Mapbox determines it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 above. In determining how long to retain personal data, Mapbox considers the amount, nature and sensitivity of the data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data, the purposes for which personal data is processed, applicable legal requirements, and Mapbox’s legitimate interests. The purposes for which Mapbox processes data may dictate different retention periods for the same types of data. For example, Mapbox retains IP addresses for 30 days and after such time, in select instances, may need to extend such retention period for an investigation based on its legitimate interests to secure its products and services, prevent fraud and for legal compliance purposes.

### **Security**

Mapbox takes steps designed to secure personal data in accordance with this product privacy policy.  Unfortunately, no system is 100% secure, and Mapbox cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal data it receives.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Mapbox does not accept liability for unintentional or accidental destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access.

### **Children**

Mapbox products and services are not intended or directed to children under the age of 18 (or other age of majority as required by local law), and Mapbox does not knowingly collect personal data from children. If the parent or legal guardian learns that their child has provided Mapbox with personal data without their consent, then they should contact Mapbox as set forth below in the Contact Mapbox section of this product privacy policy. If Mapbox learns that it has collected personal data in violation of applicable data protection laws and regulations, it will promptly take steps to delete such personal data.

### **Choices About Personal Data** 

To the fullest extent possible, Mapbox will fulfill data subject rights requests provided it can match a data subject (natural person to whom the personal data in question pertains) to personal data that Mapbox processes. Mapbox does not, and is not required to, collect additional personal data in order to positively identify a data subject. 

As outlined in Section 1 above, Mapbox receives only minimal personal data and operates controls designed to promptly de-identify and anonymize such personal data. For example, Mapbox deletes IP addresses within 30 days of receipt (unless required for an investigation), so it is unlikely that Mapbox would have personal data capable of identifying a data subject after 30 days of receiving such data. However, if verifiable and detailed information is available, Mapbox will work with the data subject to determine if the request can reasonably be met. The data subject will need to provide a valid email address so that Mapbox can communicate and support the request, as well as any information that Mapbox determines may be needed to verify whether it holds any applicable personal data. 

**In accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations and depending upon the data subject’s residency, the data subject to whom the personal data pertains may have the right to request the following regarding certain of their personal data:**

* Access/view/know personal data  
* Portability of personal data in a commonly machine readable format 
* Correct personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete
* Deletion of certain personal data
* Restrict or object to processing of personal data
* Opt-out of the “sale” or “share” or processing for “targeted advertising” (each as defined by applicable data protection laws and regulations) of personal data , if applicable, where such requests are permitted by law

To request deletion of certain personal data, please complete the form [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/ccpa-deletion-request#:~:text=To%20delete%20account%2Drelated%20information,you%20believe%20Mapbox%20obtained%20it.). For any other request to exercise rights, please contact Mapbox at [privacy@mapbox.com](mailto:privacy@mapbox.com). The requesting email must come from the data subject to whom the personal data pertains and include the data subject’s name, email address and specific request or question. To protect privacy, Mapbox will take steps to verify the identity of the requestor before fulfilling the request. Mapbox will process such requests in accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations. 

To the extent required in the state where the data subject resides and where Mapbox has denied such data subject’s earlier request, the data subject may file an appeal with Mapbox for reconsideration. To file an appeal, please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com. The requesting email must come from the data subject to whom the personal data pertains and include the data subject’s name, email address and reference to the specific request and denial.

Mapbox encourages data subjects to contact it directly with any questions or complaints. However, Mapbox acknowledges and informs the data subject that they have the right to lodge a complaint in the EU and UK with the appropriate supervisory authority in the applicable jurisdiction; .; and in select United States states, to contact the respective state’s Attorney General’s Office, whose contact information may be identified here https://www.usa.gov/state-attorney-general (or successor link). In some cases, these rights may be subject to exceptions, as permitted by applicable law.

### **Additional Information For California Residents**

##### **9.1 California Notice At Collection:**

**Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to its product development and operations in an effort to collect the least amount of personal data from the outset. The limited personal dataset that Mapbox may receive, outlined below, describes personal data categories and associated example data elements.  Please note, many data elements are only classified as personal data when combined with an associated IP address, other persistent identifier or data element capable of identifying or being reasonably linked to a natural person.

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s company name (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name. |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(an IP address is not associated with such geolocation data and the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

‍

**Dash branded products and services:** In addition to the above categories of personal data, Mapbox may also collect the following categories of personal data (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

‍

##### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data** 

Mapbox does not process personal data for the purposes of identifying an individual or creating or maintaining records about an individual. Instead, Mapbox processes personal data to:       

* Provide, test, maintain, secure and improve Mapbox products and services, 
* Provide customer requested support, including applying knowledge gained from individual customer support requests to benefit all Mapbox customers, to the extent such knowledge is de-identified,
* Prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks,
* Administer/bill customers (not end users),
* Calculate de-identified aggregate statistics,
* Train artificial intelligence models (to the extent personal data is first de-identified), which is a set of technologies and processes that allow computers to learn, reason, and assist in decision making; such models are used to improve Mapbox products and services,
* Anonymize such data so it is no longer considered personal data,
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations, and 
* Comply with applicable law.

Mapbox processes de-identified data only in a de-identified form and does not permit attempts to re-identify such data or associate with a natural person.

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above uses of personal data, Mapbox may also use personal data in the following ways (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Mapbox uses personal data for purposes that are compatible with those stated above such as providing and supporting the service. For Dash branded products and services, machine learning to develop and improve and fine tune Mapbox’s models is one of those purposes.
* Third party independent controller vendors will process the data you provide to Dash branded products and services for their own purposes. For more information visit their respective privacy policies (linked in Section 3). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

##### **To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**  

**Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to process in accordance  with Section 2 above.
* In response to a request, so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its customers or their end users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or due diligence related thereto of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

**Dash branded products and services:** In addition to the above parties that Mapbox may disclose personal data to, Mapbox may also disclose personal data to the following third party independent controllers (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Certain functionality to instruct Dash branded products and services to process a question such as when the end user says “hey Dash” or touches the Dash branded products and services icon or starts typing a command. PicoVoice’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://picovoice.ai/docs/privacy-policy/  (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* On-device speech-to-text (“STT”) vendor (which Mapbox has no control over and is selected by the end user based on their device) will transpose audio speech spoken to Dash branded products and services to a string of text and send it to Mapbox servers to answer the end users question. The on-device STT processing is subject to its respective published privacy practices, which you should review. Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Large language model providers (“LLMs”), such as OpenAI review the end users voice input text and formulate a response to the end user. OpenAI’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://openai.com/policies/privacy-policy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Text-to-speech (“TTS”) vendors, such as Eleven labs transform the Mapbox appended LLM response to an audio MP3 file that is spoken (in audio form) to the requestor via Dash branded products and services. ElevenLabs processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://elevenlabs.io/privacy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍**Data Retention**

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as Mapbox determines it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 above. In determining how long to retain personal data, Mapbox considers the amount, nature and sensitivity of the data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data, the purposes for which personal data is processed, applicable legal requirements, and Mapbox’s legitimate interests. The purposes for which Mapbox processes data may dictate different retention periods for the same types of data. For example, Mapbox retains IP addresses for 30 days and after such time, in select instances, may need to extend such retention period for an investigation based on its legitimate interests to secure its products and services, prevent fraud and for legal compliance purposes.

### **Changes to this Product Privacy Policy**

Mapbox will update this product privacy policy at its own discretion from time to time to reflect changes in Mapbox’s practices, technologies, legal requirements, and other factors. 

### **Contact Mapbox** 

Mapbox would love to hear any questions, concerns, or feedback about this product privacy policy or Mapbox’s data protection practices. Please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com.

Heading 1
=========

Heading 2
---------

### Heading 3

#### Heading 4

##### Heading 5

###### Heading 6

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur.

> Block quote

Ordered list

1. Item 1
2. Item 2
3. Item 3

Unordered list

* Item A
* Item B
* Item C

**Bold text**

_Emphasis_

Superscript

Subscript

Privacy & Security FAQ
----------------------

Last Updated:  Aug 22, 2023

1\. What is Mapbox?

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

13\. More questions?

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

### Want to receive updates on our sub-processors?

Please subscribe below:

Stay tuned for updates!

Please enter an email address that includes @.

‍**Mapbox Privacy Policies**
============================

* ‍[Privacy Policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)
* ‍[Product Privacy Policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy)

[**‍**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy)**California Notices At Collection**

* ‍[Privacy Policy "California Notice At Collection"](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#[AIFCAIFC])

Privacy Policy
--------------

This privacy policy describes the personal data Mapbox and/or its affiliates (hereinafter collectively referred to as “Mapbox”) may receive and why such personal data may be received in its capacity as a data controller, how such personal data may be used (including whom it may be shared with and for what purposes), and choices about such personal data.    

This privacy policy applies to the extent Mapbox processes personal data in its capacity as a data controller under the GDPR (or “business” under the CCPA) when an individual: (a) visits and engages with any of Mapbox’s websites, (b) attends a virtual or in-person Mapbox event, (c) provides contact information for the purposes of Mapbox contacting about Mapbox products/services, (d) uses third-party websites or applications that cite this privacy policy, (e) provide billing information for Mapbox products/services account administration, or (f) apply to or are contacted about possible employment with Mapbox. Personal data is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household, as defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.100 et seq. and its implementing regulations (“CCPA”), or relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (hereinafter referred to as "personal data").

This Privacy Policy does not apply when Mapbox acts as a data processor.  Most Mapbox customer personal data is not governed by this policy. Mapbox operates in the capacity of a data processor for certain personal data when operating Mapbox’s  products/services that are purchased by developers and businesses to develop their own licensed applications. As such, customers/prospective customers should read Mapbox’s data processing addendum (“DPA”): [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa) which governs certain customer personal data that may be processed through use of Mapbox products/services including creation of a Mapbox products/services account. For other data not Processed by Mapbox as a Processor, e.g. billing and usage statistics data, see [**Mapbox's Product Privacy Policy**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy#product-privacy-policy).

Corporate Accounts: If any account created with Mapbox lists a corporate email address for a company with which an individual is currently (or was formerly) employed (a “Corporate Email”), then the corporate entity to whom the Corporate Email pertains is responsible for privacy practices relating to use of Corporate Email. If Corporate Email is used within the scope of this privacy policy (as described at the top of this privacy policy), then this privacy policy applies.  For clarification, commonly known personal email account services (e.g., Gmail, Yahoo, Outlook) are not Corporate Email.  

### **Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**     

* **‍**Identifiers: Such as, name, address, email, phone number, Mapbox account username.
* Commercial information: Such as, transaction data including billing contact’s name, work phone number, work email, work address, professional title, and company name. 
* Financial data: Such as, credit card data is _not_ processed by Mapbox. Instead, credit card data is processed by Stripe, a third-party PCI-certified payment service provider, in accordance with its [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
* Internet or other network or device activity: When visiting any Mapbox websites, Mapbox automatically receives certain information such as: (a) browser and device type, (b) operating system, and (c) referring web pages including the pages visited on such sites. And information such as, IP address, data collected via strictly necessary and accepted website cookies / similar technologies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website, settings, and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* Employment data: Such as, education and employment history and other relevant personal data provided in an employment application submitted to Mapbox, information from a background check including information provided from reference checks.
* Location information: Such as, the location of an event where an individual signed up to receive communication or interact with Mapbox.
* User-generated content: Such as, a public comment provided by an individual in a Mapbox hosted webinar, Mapbox blog, or like Mapbox forum. For avoidance of doubt, an individual’s Mapbox product/service feedback does not constitute user-generated content. 
* Inference data about an individual: Such as, services Mapbox thinks an individual may be interested in based on prior purchases or website browsing, subject to the [Mapbox cookie policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 
* Other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with an individual: Such as, contents of correspondence with: 1) a Mapbox service provider in order to bill for items that may have been shipped upon an individual’s request as a result of the individual’s engagement with a Mapbox marketing campaign in person or virtually. 2) Mapbox, whether received through a form submitted on its website, conversation (in person, virtual, or phone call) with its staff, or via an email sent to an \[at\]mapbox email account. 3) And such as, personal data from entities who provide personal data about individuals, their job functions, and the companies they work for. Such entities attests to Mapbox that they have obtained all necessary consents and have lawful grounds to share such personal data with Mapbox.

### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data**      

##### **Mapbox uses personal data to:**       

* Provide, test, maintain/support, secure and improve Mapbox’s websites, to prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks, to calculate de-identified aggregate statistics, and for account administration/ billing purposes. 
* Send marketing information, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications (e.g., marketing newsletters, telemarketing calls, SMS or push notifications, information about Mapbox products, news or events) about Mapbox, its affiliates and partners.
* Plan or host virtual or in person events, contests, or other programs.
* Create and manage the recruitment system, job applications and a database of interested individuals and leads (including verifying the information provided to Mapbox) and assess and evaluate applicants skills and qualifications against the position(s) applied for.
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations.  
* Comply with applicable law.

### ‍**To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**    

##### **Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to provide any of the services, or related services to those, outlined in Section 2 of this privacy policy. However, prior to sharing personal data with such parties, Mapbox will have a written agreement consistent with the obligations outlined in applicable data protection laws and regulations.                                                                           
* Advertising and analytics partners. Any secondary use or sharing of personal data obtained through the use of third party cookies by these third parties is subject to their respective privacy policies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* In response to a request so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

### ‍**International Transfers**

Personal data may be processed by one or more Mapbox affiliates, processors, or service providers in order to operate Mapbox’s business – for example, in the United States for account administration and billing. Therefore, personal data may be processed outside of the location from which it was received. Mapbox ensures that the transfer of personal data offers an adequate level of protection and security, for instance by entering into the appropriate agreements that continuously ensure the same level of protective measures as set forth in applicable data protection laws and regulations and certification certification under the EU-US Data Privacy Framework, UK Extension to the EU-US Data Privacy Framework, and the Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework (collectively, the “Data Privacy Framework” or “DPF”), and, if required, standard contractual clauses or alternative mechanism for the transfer of data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR) or other applicable regulators or legislators. 

Mapbox’s Notice of Certification under the DPF, is available here: [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification)

##### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR INDIVIDUALS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

##### **4.1 Legal bases for processing personal data:** 

Some countries require that companies only process personal data if they have a “legal basis” (or justifiable need) to process personal data. To the extent those laws apply, Mapbox’s legal bases to process personal data are as follows:

* To comply with a legal obligation to which Mapbox, as a controller, is subject.
* To protect the vital interests of an individual or of another natural person.
* For the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Mapbox as the controller or by an independent third party controller, except where the individual’s interests or fundamental rights and freedoms override such interests.
* Performance of the contract.
* Consent.

In all cases of data processing on the basis of legitimate interests, Mapbox considers the impact on the rights and freedoms of the individuals whose data may be part of the processing, and ensures that its processing activities do not contradict or place at unreasonable risk any such rights or freedoms. Mapbox has assessed that these legitimate interests are not overridden by the data protection interests or fundamental rights of any individuals. In all cases, Mapbox ensures that such processing is legal, fair, and reasonable. 

### **Retention** 

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 of this privacy policy.

### **Security**

Mapbox takes steps designed to secure personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.  Unfortunately, no system is 100% secure, and Mapbox cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal data it receives.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Mapbox does not accept liability for unintentional or accidental destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access.**‍**

### **Children**

Mapbox products/services, websites, events, and other communications are not intended or directed to children under the age of 18 (or other age of majority as required by local law), and Mapbox does not knowingly collect personal data from children. If the parent or legal guardian learns that their child has provided Mapbox with personal data without their consent, then they should contact Mapbox as set forth below in the Contact Mapbox section of this privacy policy. If Mapbox learns that it has collected personal data in violation of applicable law, it will promptly take steps to delete such personal data.

### **Choices About Personal Data**

An individual may opt-out of processing of their personal data within the scope of this privacy policy at any time and prevent further Mapbox processing by contacting Mapbox as described below. 

* **Email and Telephone Communications:**

Click the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email received from Mapbox to opt out of receiving future commercial emails. Note that for current customers, Mapbox will continue to send non-promotional communications which may not be opted out of (e.g., communications regarding products/services or updates to Mapbox Terms or this privacy policy). Mapbox processes requests to be placed on do-not-mail, do-not-phone, and do-not-contact lists as required by applicable law.

* **Website logs and cookies:**

Devices have settings to delete stored cookies and most browsers have the option to decline cookies. However, certain parts of Mapbox’s website (including pages that require login) will not be accessible if Mapbox cookies (first party cookies) are not accepted. In contrast, third-party cookies set by third parties for marketing and analytics purposes on Mapbox’s website can be disabled, in principle, without affecting access. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit the Mapbox website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 

* **In accordance with applicable law, the individual to whom the personal data pertains may have the following rights regarding their personal data:**

* Access/view personal data  
* Portability of personal data in a commonly machine readable format 
* Correct personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete
* Deletion of personal data
* Restrict or object to processing of personal data
* Opt-out of the sale of personal data, if applicable, where such requests are permitted by law and as defined in the CCPA.

To exercise your right to deletion of personal data, please complete the form [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/ccpa-deletion-request#:~:text=To%20delete%20account%2Drelated%20information,you%20believe%20Mapbox%20obtained%20it.). For any other rights, please contact Mapbox at [privacy@mapbox.com](mailto:privacy@mapbox.com). In your email include  name, and request or question. To protect privacy, Mapbox will take steps to verify the identity of the requestor before fulfilling the request. Mapbox will process such requests in accordance with applicable laws. Although we encourage you to contact us if you have questions or complaints, you also have the right to lodge a complaint in the EU and UK with the appropriate supervisory authority in your jurisdiction. In some cases, these rights may be subject to exceptions, as permitted by applicable law. 

### **Additional Information For California Residents**

##### **9.1 California Notice At Collection:**

**Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**

* **‍**Identifiers: Such as, name, address, email, phone number, Mapbox account username.
* Commercial information: Such as, transaction data including billing contact’s name, work phone number, work email, work address, professional title, and company name. 
* Financial data: Such as, credit card data is _not_ processed by Mapbox. Instead, credit card data is processed by Stripe, a third-party PCI-certified payment service provider, in accordance with its [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
* Internet or other network or device activity: When visiting any Mapbox websites, Mapbox automatically receives certain information such as: (a) browser and device type, (b) operating system, and (c) referring web pages including the pages visited on such sites. And information such as, IP address, data collected via strictly necessary and accepted website cookies / similar technologies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website, settings, and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* Employment data: Such as, education and employment history and other relevant personal data provided in an employment application submitted to Mapbox, information from a background check including information provided from reference checks.
* Location information: Such as, the location of an event where an individual signed up to receive communication or interact with Mapbox.
* User-generated content: Such as, a public comment provided by an individual in a Mapbox hosted webinar, Mapbox blog, or like Mapbox forum. For avoidance of doubt, an individual’s Mapbox product/service feedback does not constitute user-generated content. 
* Inference data about an individual: Such as, services Mapbox thinks an individual may be interested in based on prior purchases or website browsing, subject to the [Mapbox cookie policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies). 
* Other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with an individual: Such as, contents of correspondence with: 1) a Mapbox service provider in order to bill for items that may have been shipped upon an individual’s request as a result of the individual’s engagement with a Mapbox marketing campaign in person or virtually. 2) Mapbox, whether received through a form submitted on its website, conversation (in person, virtual, or phone call) with its staff, or via an email sent to an \[at\]mapbox email account. 3) And such as, personal data from entities who provide personal data about individuals, their job functions, and the companies they work for. Such entities attests to Mapbox that they have obtained all necessary consents and have lawful grounds to share such personal data with Mapbox.

**How Mapbox Uses Personal Data** 

* Provide, test, maintain/support, secure and improve Mapbox’s websites, to prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks, to calculate de-identified aggregate statistics, and for account administration/ billing purposes. 
* Send marketing information, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications (e.g., marketing newsletters, telemarketing calls, SMS or push notifications, information about Mapbox products, news or events) about Mapbox, its affiliates and partners.
* Plan or host virtual or in person events, contests, or other programs.
* Create and manage the recruitment system, job applications and a database of interested individuals and leads (including verifying the information provided to Mapbox) and assess and evaluate applicants skills and qualifications against the position(s) applied for.
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations.  
* Comply with applicable law.

**To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**  

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to provide any of the services, or related services to those, outlined in Section 2 of this privacy policy. However, prior to sharing personal data with such parties, Mapbox will have a written agreement consistent with the obligations outlined in applicable data protection laws and regulations.                                                                           
* Advertising and analytics partners. Any secondary use or sharing of personal data obtained through the use of third party cookies by these third parties is subject to their respective privacy policies. For information about cookies on Mapbox’s website and how to change browser cookie settings, please visit Mapbox’s website [**here**](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/cookies).
* In response to a request so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

**Data Retention**

* Only for so long as Mapbox has a business purpose to retain and process such personal data.                                                      

### **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

Mapbox will update this privacy policy at its own discretion from time to time to reflect changes in Mapbox’s practices, technologies, legal requirements, and other factors. **‍**

### **Contact Mapbox** 

Mapbox would love to hear any questions, concerns, or feedback about this privacy policy or Mapbox’s data protection practices. Please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com.

* * *

**Mapbox Product Privacy Policy**
---------------------------------

**See Section 9 below for "California Notice At Collection"**

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers map and location services in a wide variety of web, mobile, game and embedded device applications. Mapbox customers are developers/companies who embed Mapbox software development kits (SDKs) or integrate with Mapbox application program interfaces (APIs) (collectively, “**Mapbox materials**”) in their licensed applications to enable maps and location features.  

**This product privacy policy** applies when Mapbox is processing personal data (sometimes referred to as personal information), from an end user of a licensed application (provided by Mapbox or one of its customers) that contains Mapbox materials, in its capacity (where legally applicable) as an independent data controller. For example, when Mapbox determines the purpose and means of processing such as making decisions about how to process personal data that benefits Mapbox customers generally, not just a single customer, Mapbox is processing as an independent data controller. In all cases, Mapbox’s processing of personal data continues to be controlled by its contracts with Mapbox customers, this product privacy policy and applicable data protection laws and regulations. 

Personal data is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, or relating to an identified or identifiable natural person, or data defined as personal information or personal data under applicable data protection laws and regulations (in this policy, referred to as "**personal data**”).

**Additional Privacy Policy:** Mapbox also processes as a data controller when individuals use any Mapbox website or engage with Mapbox marketing programs, including attending live or virtual events or applying for a job with Mapbox. Please see the applicable Mapbox privacy policy, available [here.](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)

### Personal Data Mapbox May Receive

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to its product development and operations in an effort to collect the least amount of personal data from the outset. The limited personal dataset that Mapbox may receive, outlined below, describes personal data categories and associated example data elements.  Please note, many data elements are only classified as personal data when combined with an associated IP address, other persistent identifier or data element capable of identifying or being reasonably linked to a natural person.

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

‍

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above categories of personal data, Mapbox may also collect the following categories of personal data (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

‍

### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data**

Mapbox does not process personal data for the purposes of identifying an individual or creating or maintaining records about an individual. Instead, Mapbox processes personal data to:       

* Provide, test, maintain, secure and improve Mapbox products and services, 
* Provide customer requested support, including applying knowledge gained from individual customer support requests to benefit all Mapbox customers, to the extent such knowledge is de-identified,
* Prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks,
* Administer/bill customers (not end users),
* Calculate de-identified aggregate statistics,
* Train artificial intelligence models (to the extent personal data is first de-identified), which is a set of technologies and processes that allow computers to learn, reason, and assist in decision making; such models are used to improve Mapbox products and services,
* Anonymize such data so it is no longer considered personal data,
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations, and 
* Comply with applicable law.

Mapbox processes de-identified data only in a de-identified form and does not permit attempts to re-identify such data or associate with a natural person.

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above uses of personal data, Mapbox may also use personal data in the following ways (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Mapbox uses personal data for purposes that are compatible with those stated above such as providing and supporting the service. For Dash branded products and services, machine learning to develop and improve and fine tune Mapbox’s models is one of those purposes.
* Third party independent controller vendors will process the data you provide to Dash branded products and services for their own purposes. For more information visit their respective privacy policies (linked in Section 3). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍

### **To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data** 

**Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to process in accordance  with Section 2 above. 
* In response to a request, so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its customers or their end users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or due diligence related thereto of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

Dash branded products and services: In addition to the above parties that Mapbox may disclose personal data to, Mapbox may also disclose personal data to the following third party independent controllers (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Certain functionality to instruct Dash branded products and services to process a question such as when the end user says “hey Dash” or touches the Dash branded products and services icon or starts typing a command. PicoVoice’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://picovoice.ai/docs/privacy-policy/  (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* On-device speech-to-text (“STT”) vendor (which Mapbox has no control over and is selected by the end user based on their device) will transpose audio speech spoken to Dash branded products and services to a string of text and send it to Mapbox servers to answer the end users question. The on-device STT processing is subject to its respective published privacy practices, which you should review. Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Large language model providers (“LLMs”), such as OpenAI review the end users voice input text and formulate a response to the end user. OpenAI’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://openai.com/policies/privacy-policy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Text-to-speech (“TTS”) vendors, such as Eleven labs transform the Mapbox appended LLM response to an audio MP3 file that is spoken (in audio form) to the requestor via Dash branded products and services. ElevenLabs processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://elevenlabs.io/privacy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍

### **International Transfers**

Personal data may be processed by one or more Mapbox affiliates, processors, or service providers in order to operate Mapbox’s business – for example, in the United States for account administration and billing. Therefore, personal data may be processed outside of the location from which it was received. Mapbox ensures that the transfer of personal data offers an adequate level of protection and security, for instance by entering into the appropriate agreements that continuously ensure the same level of protective measures as set forth in applicable data protection laws and regulations and certification certification under the EU-US, UK-US, Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework ("DPF"), and, if required, standard contractual clauses or alternative mechanism for the transfer of data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR) or other applicable regulators or legislators. 

Mapbox’s Notice of Certification under the DPF, is available here: [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/notice-of-certification)

##### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR INDIVIDUALS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

##### **4.1 Legal bases for processing personal data:** 

Some countries require that companies only process personal data if they have a “legal basis” (or justifiable need) to process personal data. To the extent those laws apply, Mapbox’s legal bases to process personal data are as follows:

* To comply with a legal obligation to which Mapbox, as a controller, is subject.
* To protect the vital interests of an individual or of another natural person.
* For the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Mapbox as the controller or by an independent third party controller, except where the individual’s interests or fundamental rights and freedoms override such interests.
* Performance of the contract.
* Consent.

In all cases of data processing on the basis of legitimate interests, Mapbox considers the impact on the rights and freedoms of the individuals whose data may be part of the processing, and ensures that its processing activities do not contradict or place at unreasonable risk any such rights or freedoms. Mapbox has assessed that these legitimate interests are not overridden by the data protection interests or fundamental rights of any individuals. In all cases, Mapbox ensures that such processing is legal, fair, and reasonable. 

### **Retention** 

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as Mapbox determines it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 above. In determining how long to retain personal data, Mapbox considers the amount, nature and sensitivity of the data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data, the purposes for which personal data is processed, applicable legal requirements, and Mapbox’s legitimate interests. The purposes for which Mapbox processes data may dictate different retention periods for the same types of data. For example, Mapbox retains IP addresses for 30 days and after such time, in select instances, may need to extend such retention period for an investigation based on its legitimate interests to secure its products and services, prevent fraud and for legal compliance purposes.

### **Security**

Mapbox takes steps designed to secure personal data in accordance with this product privacy policy.  Unfortunately, no system is 100% secure, and Mapbox cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal data it receives.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Mapbox does not accept liability for unintentional or accidental destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access.

### **Children**

Mapbox products and services are not intended or directed to children under the age of 18 (or other age of majority as required by local law), and Mapbox does not knowingly collect personal data from children. If the parent or legal guardian learns that their child has provided Mapbox with personal data without their consent, then they should contact Mapbox as set forth below in the Contact Mapbox section of this product privacy policy. If Mapbox learns that it has collected personal data in violation of applicable data protection laws and regulations, it will promptly take steps to delete such personal data.

### **Choices About Personal Data** 

To the fullest extent possible, Mapbox will fulfill data subject rights requests provided it can match a data subject (natural person to whom the personal data in question pertains) to personal data that Mapbox processes. Mapbox does not, and is not required to, collect additional personal data in order to positively identify a data subject. 

As outlined in Section 1 above, Mapbox receives only minimal personal data and operates controls designed to promptly de-identify and anonymize such personal data. For example, Mapbox deletes IP addresses within 30 days of receipt (unless required for an investigation), so it is unlikely that Mapbox would have personal data capable of identifying a data subject after 30 days of receiving such data. However, if verifiable and detailed information is available, Mapbox will work with the data subject to determine if the request can reasonably be met. The data subject will need to provide a valid email address so that Mapbox can communicate and support the request, as well as any information that Mapbox determines may be needed to verify whether it holds any applicable personal data. 

**In accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations and depending upon the data subject’s residency, the data subject to whom the personal data pertains may have the right to request the following regarding certain of their personal data:**

* Access/view/know personal data  
* Portability of personal data in a commonly machine readable format 
* Correct personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete
* Deletion of certain personal data
* Restrict or object to processing of personal data
* Opt-out of the “sale” or “share” or processing for “targeted advertising” (each as defined by applicable data protection laws and regulations) of personal data , if applicable, where such requests are permitted by law

To request deletion of certain personal data, please complete the form [here](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/ccpa-deletion-request#:~:text=To%20delete%20account%2Drelated%20information,you%20believe%20Mapbox%20obtained%20it.). For any other request to exercise rights, please contact Mapbox at [privacy@mapbox.com](mailto:privacy@mapbox.com). The requesting email must come from the data subject to whom the personal data pertains and include the data subject’s name, email address and specific request or question. To protect privacy, Mapbox will take steps to verify the identity of the requestor before fulfilling the request. Mapbox will process such requests in accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations. 

To the extent required in the state where the data subject resides and where Mapbox has denied such data subject’s earlier request, the data subject may file an appeal with Mapbox for reconsideration. To file an appeal, please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com. The requesting email must come from the data subject to whom the personal data pertains and include the data subject’s name, email address and reference to the specific request and denial.

Mapbox encourages data subjects to contact it directly with any questions or complaints. However, Mapbox acknowledges and informs the data subject that they have the right to lodge a complaint in the EU and UK with the appropriate supervisory authority in the applicable jurisdiction; .; and in select United States states, to contact the respective state’s Attorney General’s Office, whose contact information may be identified here https://www.usa.gov/state-attorney-general (or successor link). In some cases, these rights may be subject to exceptions, as permitted by applicable law.

### **Additional Information For California Residents**

##### **9.1 California Notice At Collection:**

**Personal Data Mapbox May Receive**

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to its product development and operations in an effort to collect the least amount of personal data from the outset. The limited personal dataset that Mapbox may receive, outlined below, describes personal data categories and associated example data elements.  Please note, many data elements are only classified as personal data when combined with an associated IP address, other persistent identifier or data element capable of identifying or being reasonably linked to a natural person.

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s company name (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name. |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(an IP address is not associated with such geolocation data and the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

‍

**Dash branded products and services:** In addition to the above categories of personal data, Mapbox may also collect the following categories of personal data (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

‍

##### **How Mapbox Uses Personal Data** 

Mapbox does not process personal data for the purposes of identifying an individual or creating or maintaining records about an individual. Instead, Mapbox processes personal data to:       

* Provide, test, maintain, secure and improve Mapbox products and services, 
* Provide customer requested support, including applying knowledge gained from individual customer support requests to benefit all Mapbox customers, to the extent such knowledge is de-identified,
* Prevent fraud, misuse and cyberattacks,
* Administer/bill customers (not end users),
* Calculate de-identified aggregate statistics,
* Train artificial intelligence models (to the extent personal data is first de-identified), which is a set of technologies and processes that allow computers to learn, reason, and assist in decision making; such models are used to improve Mapbox products and services,
* Anonymize such data so it is no longer considered personal data,
* Cooperate with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with Mapbox’s legal obligations, and 
* Comply with applicable law.

Mapbox processes de-identified data only in a de-identified form and does not permit attempts to re-identify such data or associate with a natural person.

**Dash branded products and services**: In addition to the above uses of personal data, Mapbox may also use personal data in the following ways (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Mapbox uses personal data for purposes that are compatible with those stated above such as providing and supporting the service. For Dash branded products and services, machine learning to develop and improve and fine tune Mapbox’s models is one of those purposes.
* Third party independent controller vendors will process the data you provide to Dash branded products and services for their own purposes. For more information visit their respective privacy policies (linked in Section 3). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

##### **To Whom Mapbox May Disclose Personal Data**  

**Mapbox may disclose personal data to:**

* Mapbox service providers who need to access such personal data in order to process in accordance  with Section 2 above.
* In response to a request, so long as Mapbox believes disclosure is required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. 
* If Mapbox has a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the personal data is reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of service, detect, prevent, or otherwise address threats to its platform, or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Mapbox, its customers or their end users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or due diligence related thereto of all or a portion of Mapbox’s business by another company. 

**Dash branded products and services:** In addition to the above parties that Mapbox may disclose personal data to, Mapbox may also disclose personal data to the following third party independent controllers (specific to its Dash branded products and services).

* Certain functionality to instruct Dash branded products and services to process a question such as when the end user says “hey Dash” or touches the Dash branded products and services icon or starts typing a command. PicoVoice’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://picovoice.ai/docs/privacy-policy/  (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* On-device speech-to-text (“STT”) vendor (which Mapbox has no control over and is selected by the end user based on their device) will transpose audio speech spoken to Dash branded products and services to a string of text and send it to Mapbox servers to answer the end users question. The on-device STT processing is subject to its respective published privacy practices, which you should review. Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Large language model providers (“LLMs”), such as OpenAI review the end users voice input text and formulate a response to the end user. OpenAI’s processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://openai.com/policies/privacy-policy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ processing of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.
* Text-to-speech (“TTS”) vendors, such as Eleven labs transform the Mapbox appended LLM response to an audio MP3 file that is spoken (in audio form) to the requestor via Dash branded products and services. ElevenLabs processing is subject to its published privacy practices available here: https://elevenlabs.io/privacy (or successor link). Mapbox has no control over third party independent controllers’ use of the data that the end user provides to Dash branded products and services.

‍**Data Retention**

Mapbox stores personal data for so long as Mapbox determines it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, as described in Section 2 above. In determining how long to retain personal data, Mapbox considers the amount, nature and sensitivity of the data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data, the purposes for which personal data is processed, applicable legal requirements, and Mapbox’s legitimate interests. The purposes for which Mapbox processes data may dictate different retention periods for the same types of data. For example, Mapbox retains IP addresses for 30 days and after such time, in select instances, may need to extend such retention period for an investigation based on its legitimate interests to secure its products and services, prevent fraud and for legal compliance purposes.

### **Changes to this Product Privacy Policy**

Mapbox will update this product privacy policy at its own discretion from time to time to reflect changes in Mapbox’s practices, technologies, legal requirements, and other factors. 

### **Contact Mapbox** 

Mapbox would love to hear any questions, concerns, or feedback about this product privacy policy or Mapbox’s data protection practices. Please contact Mapbox at privacy@mapbox.com.

* * *

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP  <br>address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer  <br>to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s company name (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill)  <br>and Mapbox product name. |
| Internet or other  <br>electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, and an end user’s abandonment of a  <br>given navigation route/use of an alternate navigation route. |
| Geolocation Data | \- Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy  <br>(an IP address is not associated with such geolocation data and the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)  <br>\- Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and search  <br>results of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigation  <br>customers (not end users) in their licensed applications.  <br>\- At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobile  <br>device and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | The end users’ requests are associated with a randomly generated identifier in order for Dash  <br>branded products and services to create a short-term and temporary profile required for  <br>contextual conversations such as “hey Dash, remember the cafe you gave me directions to  <br>yesterday? …” |
| Inferences | Inferences based on microphone (including voice inputs) and location data. For example,  <br>if the end user asks about cafe’s, Dash branded products and services will infer that the  <br>end user would like to know about cafe’s close to their location. |
| Conversation Data | Microphone data (including voice inputs).  <br>Do not include sensitive information to Dash branded products and services such as social  <br>security number, bank account or other financial details, or special categories of Personal  <br>Data such as, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical  <br>beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic or biometric data, health and/or sex life. |

Heading 1
=========

Heading 2
---------

### Heading 3

#### Heading 4

##### Heading 5

###### Heading 6

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur.

> Block quote

Ordered list

1. Item 1
2. Item 2
3. Item 3

Unordered list

* Item A
* Item B
* Item C

**Bold text**

_Emphasis_

Superscript

Subscript

Privacy & Security FAQ
----------------------

Last Updated:  Aug 22, 2023

1\. What is Mapbox?

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

13\. More questions?

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

1\. What is Mapbox?

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

13\. More questions?

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

1\. What is Mapbox?

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

13\. More questions?

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

1\. What is Mapbox?

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

13\. More questions?

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

1\. What is Mapbox?

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

1\. What is Mapbox?

1\. What is Mapbox?

1\. What is Mapbox?

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

Mapbox provides a location data platform that powers maps and location services. Mapbox provides SDKs (software development kits) and APIs (application programming interfaces), which businesses and developers use to incorporate Mapbox mapping and navigation technologies into the licensed applications and websites they make. The SDKs contain libraries of software code which are incorporated into a customer’s licensed application or website. These libraries of software code facilitate API requests to Mapbox’s location data platform (which is a backend data server, hosted in the cloud (AWS-US)) which then responds with map and location content to the customer’s application or website.

In addition, Mapbox offers an on-premise version of its location data services, called Atlas.

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

2\. Does Mapbox sell personal data?

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

**No.** Mapbox does not sell personal data.

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

3\. Does Mapbox track end users or build end user profiles?

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

**No.** For customers on a monthly active user (“MAU”) billing model, Mapbox maintains counts of MAUs for billing purposes only. Mapbox does not (and cannot) track an end user’s activity across billing cycles and does not build targeted profiles with the data processed through its products/services.

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

4\. What types of personal data does Mapbox collect from end users and why?

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

| Data Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Such as randomly generated billing ID, session ID & feedback ID (if given), and IP address (to provide the service, for billing/security purposes and deleted after 30 days). |
| Commercial Information | Such as user agent, which may include an application ID (determined by the Mapbox customer to identify its application), Mapbox customer’s account ID (so that Mapbox knows which company to bill) and Mapbox product name(s) and version(s). Such as data that an individual may upload to Mapbox products/services or otherwise provide to Mapbox in connection with support, or feedback that end users voluntarily contribute to Mapbox along with their associated contact information. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Such as timestamp accompanying received data elements, an end user’s abandonment of a given navigation route / use of an alternate navigation route;  <br>Such as connectivity and device data including device model and browser information, operating system, and contents of an API or SDK request. |
| Geolocation Data | Such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy (the session ID association is broken within 24 hours.)Applies only to Navigation SDK: If Mapbox Copilot is enabled, Mapbox receives detailed full trip trace files and searchresults of navigation sessions. Mapbox Copilot is disabled by default and may only be enabled by Mapbox Navigationcustomers (not end users) in their licensed applications.At any time, end users may change their location permissions for a given licensed application through their mobiledevice and choose to disable access to location data. Such change may affect the designed functionality of the licensed application. |

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

5\. What measures does Mapbox take to minimize and protect personal data?

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

Mapbox applies the principle of data minimization to product development and operations in an effort to collect only limited  data  from  the  outset. Mapbox  operates  a  number  of  technical  and  organization measures regarding the limited personal dataset that we process, such as strict access controls and prompt deletion of raw log files that contain IP addresses and billing IDs. Mapbox deploys regular ID rotation and 1-way hashing for billing IDs, which must be retained for accounting and billing purposes, to minimize the ability  to  track  user  requests over time. Billing  IDs  are  not  transmitted with  unrelated  events,  further reducing  the  feasibility  of  correlating  a  user’s  activities  over  time.  In  addition, Mapbox operates  strict anonymization procedures, such as clipping traces, for telemetry events that send location data.

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

6\. Why are IP addresses collected?

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

Communication through the Internet requires the presence of IP addresses, which specify each transmission’s origin and destination. When end users engage with applications that access Mapbox products/services through the Internet, the end user necessarily discloses their current IP address to one or more Mapbox servers. IP addresses are retained in cloudfront logs for 30 days for billing and customer usage reporting, unless involved in an ongoing security, anti-fraud, or misuse investigation.

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

7\. Why (and when) is location data collected?

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

Mapbox receives location data when a Mapbox customer’s end users uses a licensed application that incorporates Mapbox mobile SDKs and the end user has authorized the licensed application’s use of the end user’s device location via their mobile phone or device operating system.

Location data includes fields such as latitude and longitude, altitude, horizontal and vertical accuracy, a session ID rotating every 24 hours, and origin IP address (as would any Internet communication). The IP address that accompanies location data is retained at the load balancer (where it is used for security and PUBLISHED: Aug 22, 2023https://www.mapbox.com/legal/legal-faq Mapbox Customer FAQ, Page 3billing purposes and discarded after 30 days). This IP address is not forwarded to the location telemetry processing pipeline. Location data is encrypted in transit and at rest, and is subject to the principle of least access, with the minimal number of personnel and processes having access to it in its pre-aggregated form.  
  
In the location data anonymization pipeline, the location data is then anonymized by clipping off the origin and destination of the trip and further dividing the trip into segments, which cannot be reassembled. The anonymized location data is then used to improve Mapbox mapping products, including the Traffic and Movement data products.

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

8\. Where (geographically) does Mapbox process personal data?

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

**In AWS in the United States.** However, for performance purposes, Mapbox regularly caches content on its AWS content delivery network (“CDN”) located in various regions. Mapbox employees who work for Mapbox wholly-owned subsidiaries may access personal data from the countries where they work in order to support, develop and provide Mapbox products/services.

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

9\. Can Mapbox limit its geographic processing to Europe (or another specific region)?

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

**No.** Mapbox’s products/services store and serve source data from an AWS primary region in the US. As noted above, data is cached and served out of various regions outside the US for performance reasons, however Mapbox cannot serve its data from one limited geographic region. To comply with GDPR and safeguard transfers to the US and other countries, please see [Mapbox's DPA, Schedule C](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/dpa), which includes the Standard Contractual Clauses released in 2021 by the European Commission.

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

10\. Does Mapbox conduct data processing impact assessments (DPIA)?

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

**Yes.** Mapbox carefully scrutinizes the personal data it processes within its engineering lifecycle, which includes conducting a privacy review for new (or changed) processing activities. Mapbox follows privacy-by-design principles and works diligently to limit the personal data it processes from the outset. A DPIA is conducted in any situation in which processing of personal data may be considered high risk and not able to be accomplished in a lower risk manner.

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

11\. How does Mapbox manage compliance with global privacy laws?

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

**Mapbox runs a global data protection program designed to operate in compliance with applicable global privacy laws, including: VCDPA** (Virginia, USA), **UCPA** (Utah, USA), **UK-GDPR** (UK), **TIPA** (Tennessee, USA), **TDPSA** (Texas, USA),**PIPEDA** (Canada), **MTCDPA** (Montana, USA), **LGPD** (Brazil),**IDPL** (Iowa, USA), **ICDPA**(Indianna, USA), **GDPR** (Europe), **CTDPA** (Connecticut, USA), **CCPA** and its implementing regulations including **CPRA** (California, USA), **CPA** (Colorado, USA), and **APPI** (Japan), among many other important jurisdictions.  
‍  
Mapbox’s privacy program is based on privacy by design, which includes monitoring for upcoming privacy laws and regulations to assess whether its practices may need to be adjusted to maintain compliance; product/service privacy reviews; data breach response processes; and operationalized technical and organizational measures designed to ensure the security of the personal data it receives including: security audits and SOC2 certification; anonymization & pseudonymization of personal data (where applicable); strict access control with logging; limited data retention periods.

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

12\. Does Mapbox have information security credentials?

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

**Yes.** Mapbox is SOC2 Type 2 certified with a [summary SOC3 report available for customer review](https://www.mapbox.com/platform/security). In addition, Mapbox earned and maintains Trusted Information Security Assessment Exchange (“TISAX”) and ISO 9001 certifications. Upon request and execution of an NDA, Mapbox may share a copy of its latest SOC2 report.

13\. More questions?

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

13\. More questions?

13\. More questions?

13\. More questions?

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

Mapbox welcomes any further questions you may have regarding its ongoing commitment to privacy and data security. Please contact Mapbox’s privacy office at privacy@mapbox.com.

### Want to receive updates on our sub-processors?

Please subscribe below:

Stay tuned for updates!

Please enter an email address that includes @.

Stay tuned for updates!

Please enter an email address that includes @.

Stay tuned for updates!

Stay tuned for updates!

Please enter an email address that includes @.

Please enter an email address that includes @.

### PRODUCTS

### Maps

### Search

### Other

### \_

### Navigation

### Logistics

### Data

### solutions

### use cases

### Developers

### Resources

### Company

* [Careers
    
    HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)

All Rights Reserved © Mapbox

### PRODUCTS

### Maps

### Search

### Other

### \_

### Navigation

### Logistics

### Data

### solutions

### use cases

### Developers

### Resources

### Company

* [Careers
    
    HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)

Home page

### PRODUCTS

### Maps

### Search

### Other

### Maps

### Search

### Other

### \_

### Navigation

### Logistics

### Data

### Navigation

### Logistics

### Data

### solutions

### use cases

### Developers

### Resources

### Developers

### Resources

### Company

* [Careers
    
    HIRING](https://www.mapbox.com/careers)

Careers

HIRING

HIRING

All Rights Reserved © Mapbox

All Rights Reserved © Mapbox

All Rights Reserved © Mapbox

All Rights Reserved © Mapbox

All Rights Reserved © Mapbox

Visit Mapbox on Github

Visit Mapbox on Github

Visit Mapbox on Twitter

Visit Mapbox on LinkedIn

Visit Mapbox on Github

Visit Mapbox on Twitter

Visit Mapbox on Github
